<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
 This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site.
 It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content.
 You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another.
 This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site.

 To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps:
 1. Log in to that site as an administrator.
 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel.
 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list.
 4. Activate & Run Importer.
 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page.
 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users
    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an
    existing user on the site or to create a new user.
 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc.
    contained in this file into your site.
-->
<!-- generator="WordPress.com" created="2023-01-20 00:12"-->
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/">
  <channel>
<title>ELECTRIC SEMATIC</title>
<link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com</link>
<description>Pathetic experience of the soul as both electric and sematic. Life as the contact point between potential difference and actual difference. --- An attempt of a self-referential spore-like ontology or knowledge-body. Must have its own neg-entropy if it actually lives, which must give a liberating energy for further actual science(s). This is the structure only, and its content will be brought forward afterwards. Works as a stepping stone, a transmutative stone. --- Slowly "obscure" sounding words must be opened. At its first stages, sadly, some over-packaging have been done.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
<language>en-GB</language>
<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
<wp:base_site_url>http://wordpress.com/</wp:base_site_url>
<wp:base_blog_url>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com</wp:base_blog_url>
<wp:author>
  <wp:author_id>228059216</wp:author_id>
  <wp:author_login>electricsemiotic</wp:author_login>
  <wp:author_email>gok.berk.ses@protonmail.com</wp:author_email>
  <wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[electricsemiotic]]></wp:author_display_name>
  <wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_first_name>
  <wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[]]></wp:author_last_name>
</wp:author>
<wp:category>
  <wp:term_id>97</wp:term_id>
  <wp:category_nicename>uncategorized</wp:category_nicename>
  <wp:category_parent/>
  <wp:cat_name><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></wp:cat_name>
</wp:category>
<generator>http://wordpress.com/</generator>
<image>
		<url>http://s0.wp.com/i/buttonw-com.png</url>
		<title>ELECTRIC SEMATIC</title>
		<link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com</link>
	</image>
	<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Home]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 02:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/home/</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:query {"queryId":8,"query":{"perPage":"10","pages":0,"offset":0,"postType":"post","order":"desc","orderBy":"date","author":"","search":"","exclude":[],"sticky":"","inherit":false},"displayLayout":{"type":"list"}} -->
<div class="wp-block-query"><!-- wp:post-template -->
<!-- wp:post-title {"isLink":true,"style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"24px","lineHeight":"1.2"}}} /-->

<!-- wp:post-featured-image {"isLink":true,"align":"wide"} /-->

<!-- wp:post-content /-->

<!-- wp:group {"layout":{"type":"flex"}} -->
<div class="wp-block-group"><!-- wp:post-date {"isLink":true,"style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"16px"}}} /-->

<!-- wp:post-terms {"term":"category","style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"16px"}}} /-->

<!-- wp:post-terms {"term":"post_tag","style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"16px"}}} /--></div>
<!-- /wp:group -->

<!-- wp:spacer {"height":"120px"} -->
<div style="height:120px" aria-hidden="true" class="wp-block-spacer"></div>
<!-- /wp:spacer -->
<!-- /wp:post-template -->

<!-- wp:query-pagination -->
<!-- wp:query-pagination-previous /-->

<!-- wp:query-pagination-next /-->
<!-- /wp:query-pagination --></div>
<!-- /wp:query -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>2</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2022-12-28 02:53:29</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2022-12-28 02:53:29</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-05 01:40:22</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-04 22:40:22</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>home</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>sharing_disabled</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;N;}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>switch_like_status</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;N;}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_starter_page_template</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[blank]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_hs_old_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[29]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[header-footer-only]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_pending</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Hello World!]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2022/12/28/hello-world/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 02:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2022/12/28/hello-world/</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Welcome to WordPress! This is your first post. Edit or delete it to take the first step in your blogging journey.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>3</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2022-12-28 02:53:28</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2022-12-28 02:53:28</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2022-12-28 02:53:28</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2022-12-28 02:53:28</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>hello-world</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_headstart_post</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[_hs_extra]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>sharing_disabled</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;N;}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>switch_like_status</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;N;}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_starter_page_template</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_hs_old_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[4]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wpas_skip_all_services</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_pending</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Custom Styles]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2022/12/28/wp-global-styles-pub%2fzoologist/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 03:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2022/12/28/wp-global-styles-pub%2fzoologist/</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"version":2,"isGlobalStylesUserThemeJSON":true}]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>4</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2022-12-28 06:08:32</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2022-12-28 03:08:32</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2022-12-28 06:08:32</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2022-12-28 03:08:32</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>wp-global-styles-pub%2fzoologist</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>wp_global_styles</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="wp_theme" nicename="zoologist"><![CDATA[zoologist]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_pending</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[PS, Germ Theory, Serotonin, Peat]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/ps-germ-theory-serotonin-peat/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 03:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?page_id=5</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Key to understanding PS is to understand what is "the rigidity of soul," and thus rigidity of matter. Serotonin and anti-serotonin experiences calibrate exactly with regard to this. Serotonin exactly does this rigidifying, sedimenting, coagulating effect upon the liquid crystalline structure, i.e. life. It literally coagulates one's blood. It literalizes.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Theoretical poles represented by Louis Pasteur and Antoine Bechamp before the beginning of the century, can hint us a biological route with regard to Paranoid-Schizoid position, i.e. extreme fear of bad, and elimination of complete evil, or bad, or what is poisonous to life. The modern forking of medicine naturally chooses the first pole. Medicine in its mechanical pursuit of elimination of Death does this by ignoring all the liquid "cleaning" processes of organism.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Organism is self cleaning, if somehow contaminated, it can clean itself just by living its energical life. Obsession with hygiene and sterilization, stalls exactly this energical process. Obsession of modular body parts comes after this. Hence, modern medicine. Along with organic body, every germ becomes solidified too, becomes monomorphic---contrast it with Terrainian pleomorphism and exosome theory. Only with monomorphic theory, we can evade completely from what is poisonous to body, what we call germ. Vaccines are designed exactly for this. A monomorphic ad hoc antitode, pharmakon, to a monomorphic life-threat. On the contrary, if no structure is rigid, either that of organic body or that of the germ, idea of vaccine becomes superfluous.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Paranoid-schizoid attitude, extreme distancing to bad object, tries to play "the floor is lava." If germs, i.e. what signals Death, is everywhere, then, organism must escape infinitely, by hibernating and closing completely. Isolation of inside from outside. Including non-perception and non-acting---these are the primary input and output of an organism. Perceive, act. If input and output can be eliminated, threat of Death becomes meaningless. Paranoid-Schizoid in its last shenanigan, tries to evade Perceiving and Acting. "Becoming insensitive."</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Hence complete fear regarding germs, toxicity, thus Death, itself comes with the degeneration of Life impulse. Hence, the infantile hell and agony for the new born. This may be the most distant thing from the structure-giving experience of a new born. Schizoid in its schizoid agony, is not Living, it somehow spoiled even just before it has "high metabolism." For the new born experience may be mildly fracturing, when the high energy comes, i.e. mother comes, baby mind can easily strip the schizoid injury from its present moment off, continuing its research into energetics and language, i.e. learning. But, adult baby, infantilism, could not easily does this, due to necessary catabolism of after-adolescence. Thus, baby is not schizoid, the schizoid resiudal hell of an infant can be reached excessively only in adult life. Adult infantile, mostly after its twenties, falls into and somehow loses its way, in its childhood Hell. This is the recipe, dynamics, of Paranoid-Schizoid position. Remember, most schizophrenia starts in twenties, due to the necessary hypothyroidism coming with degeneration. Similarly, mild schizophrenias, which now called Personality Disorders, also are gained their last forms around the same age.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Psyhcology and biology are interdependent in the dynamic of Paranoid-Schizoid position, as long as energy and atructure are interdependent. Biology, and biological science, must be interdependent in the same sense. Science-making is also and necessarily prone to Paranoid-Schizoid positionings, fruitfuls startings, falling short, and eventually becoming confined into its infantile hell-like states.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Pleomorphic theory, evades the Paranoid-Schizoid organic problem, by, embracing terrain. Being sick and transmission of sickness is input and output signallings of highly organized animals. Organisms throw and catch their exosomes to one another. As the inter-individual signallings of Life and Death states. Mono-cellular packages can directly form from multicellular organisms. Cellular and Multicellular-Tissue level life is interdependent and continuosly inter-forming and inter-meshing. Exosomes signal new sickness and hence anti-sickness signals. PS threat is evaded through the Death state of the particular threat to particular Life state. PS comes its anti-PS. In order to achieve new Life, you have pass its Death-threshold. This is Vonderplanitzian rites of passage: passing of the threshold of detoxification. If you still live after the Death test. A radical view to organism, may be true with a quite global look into biological re-genetics of given states. But, exactly because of this given states, it is ad hoc. It does not state how individual and local organism can achieve its new, more energetic forms. Detoxification is from inside to outside: From the guts through the organism. Guts -&gt; Blood -&gt; lymphatic system. https://raypeatforum.com/community/threads/endotoxin-and-fat-consumption.11402/  Chylomicron quality is due to fat quality. Fat regulates anti-PS power of the organism. The resulting diet is Raw Primal. Every endotoxemia can be cleansed through inside out lymphatic movement. You sweat off your Death, if it ends.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Ray Peat's anti-endotoxic stance, exactly aims the Paranoid-Schizoid problem at its guts. But it does not try to transcend PS through Anti-PS. Rather, it gives the genetics of any PS. It starts from the before, tohu-va-bohu, of a PS state. Detoxification is not homogeneously inside from outside. Rather, it is through the purging of the inside, or the constipation. If the innards of the organism is "toxic," i.e. filled with the byproducts, poo-poo of other cellular Life, poison, tocisity; then the organism try to eliminate all the poo-poo, toxicity, fecal matter, excretion starting from its outside. Inside toxicity is displaced towards outside. This is the fracturing of the organism, hence seperates its Psychology from its Biology. This is the exact dynamic of what happens in a Paranoid-Schizoid motion.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Probably, thirsting to eliminate all matter from the existence. But forgets that all cleanliness comes from the inside, both for spiritual inside, and for somatic inside: gut. Homogenized terrain ad hoc science and nutrition, in turn, negates the cleanliness, it can try every toxicity, if it lives, it lives. In one sense, PS and Anti-PS creates each other, they are determined from their negation. Both Ortodox Germ Theory and Terrain Theory fails to give the energetics of what eventually ends up as PS.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>But the genetics of PS, what happens before PS, really explains:</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Peat is germ theory par excellence, not outwardly, but inwardly. By sending the theory its energical endpoints, it becomes clear that, organism must purge its innards into outside world. Somehow, it must externalize, and internalize. It must converse its relation with outside, by its "own" externalization processes. If not, it becomes anti-germ. It must have the peristalsis. All cleanliness comes topologically. Grounding and detoxification starts by purgeing. Peristatlsis regulates PS, it regulates Death, from innards of organism to downwards, to ground. Further, quality of oxidation and stability of it, Respiration=Pneuma, is the Life force, from the upwards, to chest. Respiration is before PS. Inner-toxicity creates it. Peristalsis is of downward, Oxidation is of upward energical processes. Of Death and Life.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Resulting diet is rich in electron adsorbers, Lewis acids, quinones, stabile fats; and poor in anti-peristalsis, rancid-unsaturated fats. Upward and downward dynamism. If downward stalls, liquid circulation coagulates, hence respiration becomes externally controlled. Hence:</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Peat's stance toward the external controlling of the organism, as the problematic PS of the human world.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Does this create a PS? Exactly. This is whay we are all here, forming a new sect, which is a peculiar anti-sect. This is determined serotonergically, if any one of us does not have any amount of serotonin, probably we would not be pulled to each other, in a digital system, from our computers, forming an anti-digital stance.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>But, the degrees of serotonin cascades must be differentiated from each. One is less, other is more. And calibrating the exact feeling of what a serotonin cascade is is the exact antidote to PS, which is brough by Peat, only by Peat, in known history.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><br>+++++<br>Key to understanding PS is to understand what is "the rigidity of soul," and thus rigidity of matter. Serotonin and anti-serotonin experiences calibrate exactly with regard to this. Serotonin exactly does this rigidifying, sedimenting, coagulating effect to liquid crystalline structure, i.e. life. It coagulates one's blood.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Poles represented by Louis Pasteur and Antoine Bechamp, can exactly show us a route with regard to fear of bad, and elimination of complete evil, bad, poison. Hence modern forking of medicine. Medicine in its mechanical pursuit of elimination of Death does this by eliminating all the liquid "cleaning" processes of organism. Organism is self cleaning, if somehow contaminated, it can clean itself just by living its energical life. But, obsession with hygiene and sterilization, stalls exactly this energical process. Every germ becomes solidified too, becomes monomorphic---contrast it with Terrainian pleomorphism and exosome theory. Only with monomorphic theory, we can evade completely, vaccines are designed exactly for this. If no structure is rigid, idea of vaccine becomes superfluous.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Paranoid-schizoid, extreme distancing to bad object, attitude par excellence, tries to play "the floor is lava." If germs, i.e. Death, is everywhere, then, organism escapes infinitely, by hibernating and closing completely. Into non-perception and non-acting. If input and output can be eliminated, threat of Death becomes meaningless. Complete fear regarding germs, toxicity, thus Death, itself comes with the degeneration of Life impulse. Hence, the infantile hell and agony for the new born. This may be the most distant thing from the structure-giving experience of a new born. Baby in its schizoid agony, is not Living, it somehow spoiled even just before it has "high metabolism." -- This is exactly the state which adult infantile, mostly after its twenties, falls into and somehow loses its way. Remember, most schizophrenia starts in twenties, due to the necessary hypothyroidism coming with degeneration.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Pleomorphic theory, evades the Paranoid-Schizoid organic problem, by, embracing terrain. Being sick and transmission of sickness is the package input and output signallings of highly organized animals and nothing more basic than that. Mono-cellular packages can directly form frum multicellular organisms. Cellular and Multicellular-Tissue level life is interdependent and continuosly inter-forming and inter-meshing. Exosome signal new anti-sickness signals, if organisms pass the threshold of detoxification. Detoxification is done from the guts through the organism. Guts -&gt; Blood -&gt; lymphatic system.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>https://raypeatforum.com/community/threads/endotoxin-and-fat-consumption.11402/</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Chylomicron quality is due to fat quality. Fat regulates anti-PS power of the organism.The resulting diet is Raw.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Ray Peat's anti-endotoxic stance, exactly aims the Paranoid-Schizoid problem at its guts. If the innards of the organism is "toxic," i.e. filled with the byproducts, poo-poo, of other cellular Life, then the organism try to eliminate all the poo-poo, toxicity, fecal matter, excretion from its outside. Probably, thirsting to eliminate all matter from the existence. But forgets that all cleanliness comes from the inside, both for spiritual inside, and for somatic inside: gut.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Peat is germ theory par excellence, not outwardly, but inwardly. By sending the theory its energical endpoints, it becomes clear that, organism must purge its innards into outside world. Somehow, it must externalize, and internalize. It must converse its relation with outside, by its "own" externalization processes. If not, it becomes anti-germ. It must have the peristalsis. All cleanliness comes topologically. Grounding and detoxification starts by purgeing. Peristatlsis regulates PS, it regulates Death, from innards of organism to downwards, to ground. Further, quality of oxidation and stability of it, Respiration=Pneuma, is the Life force, from the upwards, to chest. Respiration is before PS. Inner-toxicity creates it. Peristalsis is of downward, Oxidation is of upward energical processes. Of Death and Life.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Resulting diet is rich in electron adsorbers, Lewis acids, quinones, stabile fats; and poor in anti-peristalsis, rancid-unsaturated fats. Upward and downward dynamism. If downward stalls, liquid circulation coagulates, hence respiration becomes externally controlled. Hence:</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Peat's stance toward the external controlling of the organism, as the problematic PS of the human world.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>5</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2022-12-28 06:10:57</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2022-12-28 03:10:57</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2022-12-28 20:51:11</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2022-12-28 17:51:11</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>ps-germ-theory-serotonin-peat</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_pending</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>jetpack_seo_noindex</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_jetpack_post_was_ever_published</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_starter_page_template</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[blank]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_oembed_b7d8af6d6f8490470641fe6d00bc07d3</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[header]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/01/header/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 01:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/01/header/</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:group {"className":"gapless-group","layout":{"inherit":"true","type":"constrained"}} -->
<div class="wp-block-group gapless-group"><!-- wp:group {"align":"full","style":{"spacing":{"padding":{"bottom":"var(\u002d\u002dwp\u002d\u002dcustom\u002d\u002dgap\u002d\u002dvertical)","top":"var(\u002d\u002dwp\u002d\u002dcustom\u002d\u002dgap\u002d\u002dvertical)"}}},"className":"site-header site-header-linear","layout":{"type":"flex","justifyContent":"space-between"}} -->
<div class="wp-block-group alignfull site-header site-header-linear" style="padding-top:var(--wp--custom--gap--vertical);padding-bottom:var(--wp--custom--gap--vertical)"><!-- wp:group {"className":"site-brand","layout":{"type":"flex"}} -->
<div class="wp-block-group site-brand"><!-- wp:site-logo {"width":64} /-->

<!-- wp:group {"className":"site-words-stack-small","layout":{"type":"flex","justifyContent":"center"}} -->
<div class="wp-block-group site-words-stack-small"><!-- wp:site-title /-->

<!-- wp:site-tagline {"textAlign":"center","style":{"typography":{"fontSize":"var(\u002d\u002dwp\u002d\u002dcustom\u002d\u002dfont-sizes\u002d\u002dx-small)"}}} /--></div>
<!-- /wp:group --></div>
<!-- /wp:group -->

<!-- wp:navigation {"__unstableLocation":"primary","className":"social-links","layout":{"type":"flex","setCascadingProperties":true,"justifyContent":"right","orientation":"horizontal"},"style":{"spacing":{"margin":{"top":"0"}}}} -->
<!-- wp:page-list /-->
<!-- /wp:navigation --></div>
<!-- /wp:group --></div>
<!-- /wp:group -->

<!-- wp:spacer {"height":"90px"} -->
<div style="height:90px" aria-hidden="true" class="wp-block-spacer"></div>
<!-- /wp:spacer -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>11</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-01 04:17:29</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-01 01:17:29</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-01 04:17:29</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-01 01:17:29</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>header</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>wp_template_part</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="wp_template_part_area" nicename="header"><![CDATA[header]]></category>
  <category domain="wp_theme" nicename="zoologist"><![CDATA[zoologist]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>origin</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[theme]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_pending</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[PS, Germ Theory, Serotonin, Peat]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/01/ps-germ-theory-serotonin-peat/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 01:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=12</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>prev version in:  https://raypeatforum.com/community/threads/are-ray-peat-and-danny-roddy-paranoid-schizoids-in-the-kleinian-sense.46669/page-6#post-884714</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Key to understanding PS is to understand what is “the rigidity of soul,” and thus rigidity of matter. Serotonin and anti-serotonin experiences calibrate exactly with regard to this. Serotonin exactly does this rigidifying, sedimenting, coagulating effect upon the liquid crystalline structure, i.e. life. It literally coagulates one’s blood. It literalizes.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Theoretical poles represented by Louis Pasteur and Antoine Bechamp before the beginning of the century, can hint us a biological route with regard to Paranoid-Schizoid position, i.e. extreme fear of bad, and elimination of complete evil, or bad, or what is poisonous to life. The modern forking of medicine naturally chooses the first pole. Medicine in its mechanical pursuit of elimination of Death does this by ignoring all the liquid “cleaning” processes of organism.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Organism is self cleaning, if somehow contaminated, it can clean itself just by living its energical life. Obsession with hygiene and sterilization, stalls exactly this energical process. Obsession of modular body parts comes after this. Hence, modern medicine. Along with organic body, every germ becomes solidified too, becomes monomorphic—contrast it with Terrainian pleomorphism and exosome theory. Only with monomorphic theory, we can evade completely from what is poisonous to body, what we call germ. Vaccines are designed exactly for this. A monomorphic ad hoc antitode, pharmakon, to a monomorphic life-threat. On the contrary, if no structure is rigid, either that of organic body or that of the germ, idea of vaccine becomes superfluous.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Paranoid-schizoid attitude, extreme distancing to bad object, tries to play “the floor is lava.” If germs, i.e. what signals Death, is everywhere, then, organism must escape infinitely, by hibernating and closing completely. Isolation of inside from outside. Including non-perception and non-acting—these are the primary input and output of an organism. Perceive, act. If input and output can be eliminated, threat of Death becomes meaningless. Paranoid-Schizoid in its last shenanigan, tries to evade Perceiving and Acting. “Becoming insensitive.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Hence complete fear regarding germs, toxicity, thus Death, itself comes with the degeneration of Life impulse. Hence, the infantile hell and agony for the new born. This may be the most distant thing from the structure-giving experience of a new born. Schizoid in its schizoid agony, is not Living, it somehow spoiled even just before it has “high metabolism.” For the new born experience may be mildly fracturing, when the high energy comes, i.e. mother comes, baby mind can easily strip the schizoid injury from its present moment off, continuing its research into energetics and language, i.e. learning. But, adult baby, infantilism, could not easily does this, due to necessary catabolism of after-adolescence. Thus, baby is not schizoid, the schizoid resiudal hell of an infant can be reached excessively only in adult life. Adult infantile, mostly after its twenties, falls into and somehow loses its way, in its childhood Hell. This is the recipe, dynamics, of Paranoid-Schizoid position. Remember, most schizophrenia starts in twenties, due to the necessary hypothyroidism coming with degeneration. Similarly, mild schizophrenias, which now called Personality Disorders, also are gained their last forms around the same age.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Psyhcology and biology are interdependent in the dynamic of Paranoid-Schizoid position, as long as energy and atructure are interdependent. Biology, and biological science, must be interdependent in the same sense. Science-making is also and necessarily prone to Paranoid-Schizoid positionings, fruitfuls startings, falling short, and eventually becoming confined into its infantile hell-like states.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Pleomorphic theory, evades the Paranoid-Schizoid organic problem, by, embracing terrain. Being sick and transmission of sickness is input and output signallings of highly organized animals. Organisms throw and catch their exosomes to one another. As the inter-individual signallings of Life and Death states. Mono-cellular packages can directly form from multicellular organisms. Cellular and Multicellular-Tissue level life is interdependent and continuosly inter-forming and inter-meshing. Exosomes signal new sickness and hence anti-sickness signals. PS threat is evaded through the Death state of the particular threat to particular Life state. PS comes its anti-PS. In order to achieve new Life, you have pass its Death-threshold. This is Vonderplanitzian rites of passage: passing of the threshold of detoxification. If you still live after the Death test. A radical view to organism, may be true with a quite global look into biological re-genetics of given states. But, exactly because of this given states, it is ad hoc. It does not state how individual and local organism can achieve its new, more energetic forms. Detoxification is from inside to outside: From the guts through the organism. Guts -&gt; Blood -&gt; lymphatic system.&nbsp;<a href="https://raypeatforum.com/community/threads/endotoxin-and-fat-consumption.11402/">https://raypeatforum.com/community/threads/endotoxin-and-fat-consumption.11402/</a>&nbsp;Chylomicron quality is due to fat quality. Fat regulates anti-PS power of the organism. The resulting diet is Raw Primal. Every endotoxemia can be cleansed through inside out lymphatic movement. You sweat off your Death, if it ends.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Ray Peat’s anti-endotoxic stance, exactly aims the Paranoid-Schizoid problem at its guts. But it does not try to transcend PS through Anti-PS. Rather, it gives the genetics of any PS. It starts from the before, tohu-va-bohu, of a PS state. Detoxification is not homogeneously inside from outside. Rather, it is through the purging of the inside, or the constipation. If the innards of the organism is “toxic,” i.e. filled with the byproducts, poo-poo of other cellular Life, poison, tocisity; then the organism try to eliminate all the poo-poo, toxicity, fecal matter, excretion starting from its outside. Inside toxicity is displaced towards outside. This is the fracturing of the organism, hence seperates its Psychology from its Biology. This is the exact dynamic of what happens in a Paranoid-Schizoid motion.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Probably, thirsting to eliminate all matter from the existence. But forgets that all cleanliness comes from the inside, both for spiritual inside, and for somatic inside: gut. Homogenized terrain ad hoc science and nutrition, in turn, negates the cleanliness, it can try every toxicity, if it lives, it lives. In one sense, PS and Anti-PS creates each other, they are determined from their negation. Both Ortodox Germ Theory and Terrain Theory fails to give the energetics of what eventually ends up as PS.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>But the genetics of PS, what happens before PS, really explains:</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Peat is germ theory par excellence, not outwardly, but inwardly. By sending the theory its energical endpoints, it becomes clear that, organism must purge its innards into outside world. Somehow, it must externalize, and internalize. It must converse its relation with outside, by its “own” externalization processes. If not, it becomes anti-germ. It must have the peristalsis. All cleanliness comes topologically. Grounding and detoxification starts by purgeing. Peristatlsis regulates PS, it regulates Death, from innards of organism to downwards, to ground. Further, quality of oxidation and stability of it, Respiration=Pneuma, is the Life force, from the upwards, to chest. Respiration is before PS. Inner-toxicity creates it. Peristalsis is of downward, Oxidation is of upward energical processes. Of Death and Life.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Resulting diet is rich in electron adsorbers, Lewis acids, quinones, stabile fats; and poor in anti-peristalsis, rancid-unsaturated fats. Upward and downward dynamism. If downward stalls, liquid circulation coagulates, hence respiration becomes externally controlled. Hence:</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Peat’s stance toward the external controlling of the organism, as the problematic PS of the human world.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Does this create a PS? Exactly. This is whay we are all here, forming a new sect, which is a peculiar anti-sect. This is determined serotonergically, if any one of us does not have any amount of serotonin, probably we would not be pulled to each other, in a digital system, from our computers, forming an anti-digital stance.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>But, the degrees of serotonin cascades must be differentiated from each. One is less, other is more. And calibrating the exact feeling of what a serotonin cascade is is the exact antidote to PS, which is brough by Peat, only by Peat, in known history.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>12</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-01 04:39:14</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-01 01:39:14</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-01 04:39:14</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-01 01:39:14</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>ps-germ-theory-serotonin-peat</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1672537159]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80138941670]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[s:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1672537372]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Crux Point of Experience]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/02/crux-point-of-experience/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 02:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=14</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>add: ether as the structure, fabric of god-head, and a primary feedback relation between them as the main relation of energy and structure: result is Growth as growing, existing universe having more neg-entropy, as the transmutation of the present-infinite-god.  <em>sends us into the question of what is beyond experience. firstly makes us delve what is within experience, and what veils the experience. A monistic, holistic attempt, using the concepts potential and actual, in order to explain matter and soul. By not dualizing them. Starting from differentiality, and a touching point between potential and actual. As three difference. and in-between actualization, two ways. Residue potentialities and actualities, ways of sameness.</em></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Monistic and dualistic worldviews all collide at the same point. What is it the most fundamental aspect of our experience? And from where we can arrive? The twofoldness of question, immediacy, and what conditions this immediacy. The attitude of separating experience from its conditions is highly degenerated to the point of philosophers no longer experiencing, only word-exchanging; and scientists no longer studying causes, only crushing simulative-data. The word “condition,” first and foremost, dies, and loses its meaning. For any regeneration and regaining of the experience and of what is beyond, a real living ontology regarding "power," a levelling of powers, is needed. If everything is resulting from a primary energical contact, every output which we perceive as existing beings, can be thought of as the residue, and residual processes. Without a concept of life and death, and more energical and less energical, every concept and analysis falls apart. Such a schizphrenic attitude cancerously forms degenerating/misgenerating "similar but different" local sciences which have forgotten what it exactly studies at their outset: Stillbirths! This veils the crux point of experience, at which every new-born, every animal, probably even plant and mineral---matter and in a reverse way the most godlike, say, stars and planets---are present at. This is in fact the presence par excellence. Only human, diverges and diverges most, into simulative isolated local fake-environments, losing its presence, its gut feelings.&nbsp;This cancerous mis-generation of sciences is the last stage of civilization, over-seperation to the point that object to be studied is lost in a cancer of mind, rather, the cancerous mind studies the image of it, exactly by losing the connection of how the image is imprinted. It loses the interaction, the interface, the touching point, the surface, hence its depth. Only traces. A cancerous love makes the beloved far away from the lover in his pursuit of reaching. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>~~~</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Animal environment is the starting of what is called human, and it can end at human actions or human though-processes. This is what is ordinary for us. At what is striking to the eye: Mutability strikes first, and the corresponding changes of what is mutable. And some immutability form with first somewhat chaotic and then vortex-like concentric motion of eyes. "One" appears (I will not use "object," objects are far away from us in a real experience, in a real event). One seperated from the others, from its backgorund, which can form and deform further uniques. Always with a matter, always spirited. If eye seeks differences in "the one" it looks, it can find, but this is not cause the eye lose the tension of first background, onenesses can be nested in experience. Tensions can be bi-valenced, stacked, embedded. And change strikes, always. Not a change imperceptibe or unintelligible, but a change which is significant to the eye or the the mind. Something is worth attended. All experience of oneness is an experience of transmutation and of a significant transmutation. Though one is immutable and mutable at the same time in a unique tension, attention seeks the transmutative route. <br><br>What are the transmutables? Some are potentially, some others actually are;  which are the products of potentialization and actualization, reducing and sublimating. Naturally, former becomes more perceptible and tangible. The latter more intelligible, invisible. Former can be used by the latter. It exactly burns the matter. Matter can be lost, if there is a process consuming it. Actual processes uses its potentials, when potentials consumed, the actual usage is finished. And the byproducts as the products of transmutation remains. The analogy and the literality of the matter is very close here. At the crux point of experience is an oxidation event, what is potential as the fuel(reductant) and what is actual as the oxidizer. Charge is from the reductant to the oxidizer. And the logical relation of necessary and sufficient conditions are to be exactly matched to fuel and the oxidizer, to potential and to actual. Heraclitean intuition must be of this reality. At the fire of being, Logos burns matter. Logos burns tangible Fire. Sungazers are somewhat right. Red light is what makes one Star-like. And Heraclit is right on that Sun's being new every day. Heart of experience is both bright, visible and non-visible, and have thrustful and stacked, embedded, Changes. Light is hard to see even if visible-Ligh is matter-like, but to the seeing eye more invisible Light is promised. At the heterogeneous joint fire of existence, Invisible-Fire burns visible-Fire. This is the Logos. This is the logic of experience, of existing. (Both arrow and a triangle. And notice triangle is used to represent signification. And the fire is of triangular, or of tetrahedron.) Mind in a sense, use hot-matter (=energy as the actualization of a potential difference, or energy as vibration) to be maintain its mind-like dynamic status. Arrow of logicality is pointed from the matter-like to mind-like. There is no tangible at the end of the arrow. And this is the crux point. What is pointed at is always more hard to see. It is more subtle (subtle matter is used for hard-to-see matter in esoteric traditions), sublimated. Life is hard to see, but to the seeing eye, more Life is promised.<br><br>"The lord whose is the oracle at Delphoi neither utters nor hides his meaning, but shows it by a sign." Heraclitus, Fragment 93<br><br>"Some dogs alertly look at the thing a person is pointing at, other dogs just sniff the pointing finger. " Ray Peat. https://raypeat.com/articles/articles/cholesterol-longevity.shtml .<br><br>"Dogs bark at every one they do not know." Heraclitus, F 97<br></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Sematic: </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>"significant, indicative, serving as a sign or warning" (as of danger), 1855, from Greek sēmat-, combining form of sēma (genitive sematos) "sign" (see <a href="https://www.etymonline.com/word/semantic?ref=etymonline_crossreference">semantic</a>) + <a href="https://www.etymonline.com/word/-ic?ref=etymonline_crossreference">-ic</a>. Used especially in biology, in reference to "warning" colors, etc. (by 1890).<br>https://www.etymonline.com/word/sematic#etymonline_v_39476</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><br>Where there is matter, there is Mind-like processes or Mind. Matter itself is spiritual, exactly because of that it is the beginning of the arrow of the crux. Things transmute energy (energy as actualization of potential difference, energy as charge, or vibration) as matter(sedimentation of plasma), putting energy into concentric motion, thus gains mass(electric cause of gravity). Mind in its most general sense transmute matter, either by producing different matter, or by helding it to become discharged from elsewhere. (This transmutation occurs in all phases for living being: plasma, pneuma, liquid, and solid.) Spooky action at a distance, and mis-concept of a blackhole (and its correct understanding as torus) are quite hard Events to understand for a mechanically-disposed physicist. Sublimatory uniques using reductive uniques is close to Sema using Electricity. Sema being more Fire-like than Fire. Relation of burning, is a model for matter and mind.  But, let us not think of Minds internals are more vivid than what is potential at the crux point, because both Matter and Mind close into itself after they are separated, after the fire, the sign, of being lost its eventfulness.<br><br>Thus, to be in the event, is not to emphasize their difference and duality. To be at the interface, the exact one relation of the two is important. The former and the latter is different, and exactly that "one" difference is noticed, and not the "two" before the "one difference." This "one" as the transmutative tension is the puller of the attention. To treat the problemm as the separation of matter and mind, then we lost the touch with the crux point, we will come later from the experience, the event. Event is of before the separation.  Attention is always stand at the heart of emanation, of what is beyond to what is ordinarily known. And the attention is the eye-witness of such creation, and is itself to be emanated. Attention can be potentialized and actualized. This is the ultimate matter of Life and Death. But, complete potentialization of it cannot be perceived or thought, cannot be attended, as an impossiblity, it has a tension upon attention.<br><br>What attention is, is it potential or actual, apart from its potentialization or actualization? The actuality of actualization, it always actualizes where it looks at, of what is potential before. It must be actual in its extra-ordinary sense. But, all living being in a pareto fashion, passes its life in a trance-like, potentially actual way. Potential in attention is not the potentiality of attention. Potential in attention in a sense, almost everything which can be experienced. Someone curious is curious about the potentials in attention. But in so far as it actualizes its curiosity, it is of the actuality of attention, does so in actual attention. When such an exercise tires the curious, its attention becomes potential. No longer lives in the moment. As if it consumed enough potential value and its combustive process ends, hibernates and starts its residual proceses.  <br><br>Moment admits spatiotemporality. Here and now, as actual. There and thence, as potential. Actual both spatiotemporally (dimensions of experience) and attentively (what is in dimensions) and locally (as the one’s differentiated from whole as background, eventful ones) encapsulates potential. Within the realm of local, uniques or "one"s (do not understand it as atomic. they are transmutables. Uniques in the sense of one differentiated from all other), those immutables, those differentiables, those flowings; which can persist in dimensions, either in one orin&nbsp; another, or in both, and subject to change, locomotion, measurement, understanding, imagination, realization, description, utterance, sense; is experienced in two:</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>E-S interface:</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:list {"ordered":true} -->
<ol><!-- wp:list-item -->
<li>Electric.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item -->

<!-- wp:list-item -->
<li>Sematic.&nbsp;</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ol>
<!-- /wp:list -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(1) is what scientists call what is measurable through physical means. Or some other call material world. It is called reductant or fuel, above. Realm of matter in its most general sense. It can be the potential for higher processes. It can achieve further form. Whole electric realm is sublimated into semantic. It has meaning. Matter has meaning. From there, it can re-materialize or de-materialize. Matter is constantly created or destroyed within the scope of what is unique in finite experience. The whole dynamism comes from this principle, of charge. And notice, electric is the most hot thing one can imagine, and at the zero point of vibration, even electic sublimates. It transmutes into a Mind. The whole events in the universe, selects infinite zero points as embedded self-aware attentions, and this is the relation between the whole and the soul. The soul as what is most open to the whole, being Here and Now, present. Further, apart from zero points, there are possibly more non-zero points, vectors, as non-self-aware, one-sided-dis-embedded half-attention-likes working between absence and presence---but more on this later. To the question of how many types of attention possible, this must be related with dimensionality(one, two, three. Ibn Arabi's point-line-cube analogy; Kant's form of experience and on what conditions; Ouspenskii on the fourth dimension.), but again, this can only be answered with a life-time studying of our experience. Here and Now. Only now, tension of matter and mind seem like a bridge between dimensionalities, remembering the heterogeneity between spatial and temporal. And the contrast between causality as regularity and sequentiality (Hume) and causality as syncronicty. Whole concept of synchronicity (Jung, Bockris) shows this abrupt sequentiality of Here's and Now's, but, exact matter of syncronicity and causality will be of another entry. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Nothing is uncharged, and there is not neutral ground in nature. Everything is in flow. Matter is charged, it charges some other, and it is charged by some other. It is constantly created if any sense or experience of stability occurs Here and Now. (1) Electric is what is measurable through electric means. We weigh the mass of the matter. We check temperature, we measure the velocity, and various forces. We measure potential difference. We always measure difference with regard to what is electric. Wave, frequency, vibration aspects are the most powerful. Sequential and scalar ones as more dis-embedded. But always differences are more lively. This potential for further actuality, is always comes in potential differences, which can actualize at the crux point, electric-sematic interface.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Phases of matter are experienced throughout Life. Life itself is a very specific flux between phases. Death is decomposition, explosion-putrefaction into mostly the last stage of matter, solid, earthlike. Even then, complete death is almost impossible, just as there is no neutral ground, energy always goes some other place, some other locality, in dimensions. If dimensions are de-fined; always we have energical deficit or surplus. Plasma, gas, liquid, solid. E-S starts in Plasma and Significance. They are the most energical. The medium is ether, what serves the dimensionality. For us, Here and Now. Electric tetrahedron in etheric dodecahedron. If electric potential difference actualized it attracts attention; and transmutes. It "matters" and "means something."</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>The crux point. (2) : Electric is potentially matterlike but actually a Sema, non-matter and matters (both in the sense of making sense and making further matter). It has a meaning in big picture. This relation can be first thought as a representational relation; but this would be like dead matter. More correctly; it is like the internal and encapsulating nature of attention. Electric is encapsulated by an awareness and a value. A positivist would call it a truth value but the primordial value is not univalent. The positivist is not sensitive. The value is always context dependent and "charged." It is the causal, the powerful, sometimes "forceful." Sometimes electric cause the sematic, sometimes electric causes the electric, s c the e, s c the s. (Remember the above discussion of necessary and sufficient conditions, the tension between these causalities, it the dynamic heterogeneity of the experience. Causality and logic is causally and logically, self-referentially, or Fractally, connected. And to articulate their connection is to live the Life in the most curious way possible.) Different ways of E-S causality has different awarenesses in their attention. And attention can attend different ways throughout the causation. Think of it as a superposition of two arrows. The logical (above general combustive schema) is from E to S. But the causal can be both ways. And the attention can be of either end. This generativity has further awarenesses, units of consciousness even if it is not self-aware (Leibnitz). A depiction which resembles context independent grammars but actually context dependent:</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>eSs, eSe, sSe, sSs</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>eSss -&gt; eSs, esSs -&gt; sSs,</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>attention being always at the touching point of potential and actual. e to s is actualization; s to e potentialization. de-materialization; re-materialization. Thinking and Perceiving always consumes electricity; may go into system as Sema, may pop up as re-electrization somewhere other than Here and Now. Action, conversely from that reservedness, is re-electrized its proximal environment: To act is to dis-charge electrically, immediately within the scope of that unique energical body, or attention. Neural networks electricized, computes (not in a closed discrete way, but biological way), and dis-charge.  A neuron also Perceives, Thinks, and Acts. Dentritic, Implosive, Axonic. Attention or energical body is not different. In fact, all neural processes, and matter states a above (neuron is more than one nutritive states depending on its Platonic solid-like vibratory parametricality superimposed its toroidality; earthlike matter seem it sucks energy in just one state, with just one concentric motion. but crystals and non-crystals are different even in solidity) must have an awareness, eventfulness, even if with not-so-great-embedding.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Back to crux point; e-s is the touching point. From there, materializations, death or dying process of electric and sema continues. System no longer has an interface but parallelity. In its paralel states, system does not have combustion. But rather, parallelist causation. If one looks as post tetrahedral stages, system looks as if dualist.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Electric-charge-plasma &nbsp; &nbsp; &gt; gas&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;       &gt; liquid &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;                      &gt;solid</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;/</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>--&gt;e.s</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;\&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Sema-meaning-sense &gt;question &gt;intuition-induction-concept&gt;deduction-definition</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Etheric |&nbsp; plasma                            |&nbsp; pneuma        | liquid-structured water             | solid-crystal-earthlike</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Dodeca | tetra                                | octa               | icosa                                            | hexa&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(Dual relations are to be studied in further entries.)</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Thinking in terms of energy, frequency, vibration, (Tesla) the receptive and con-ceptive parts regarding Sema and Electric must be differentiated further, here in other places. For now, sufficiently correctly but not fully correctly,&nbsp; it can be almost mapped with Thinking and Perceiving faculties. They can be thrusted into reception and action. Action in Sema mostly speaks, utters, sometimes thinks further. Action in Electric, electricizes, either by motion of push and pull of bodies (in macro-scale, it is called gravity, in micro scale it is called love-or-warfare), or by staying at an interface between bodies, steering, “cybernetikos,” governed mostly by “Hand.” Action in Five senses is mostly below the level of after plasma. Plasma is mostly unseen as EMF(invisible part of spectrum used for interfacings between Electric bodies, it the Sema of Electricity) or can be seen as bright light and light brightens the eye melting the differences between seen and seer but creates confusion when transition into more dark environment. Mostly, electric it its lively states is invisible, at least not visible like everyday objects, not visible like solidity. State of gas can be seen if the gas is opaque, but mostly it is translucent, opaqueness admit likeness of solidity. Pneuma, called life-force as ancients, held by living bodies, as their breathing principles. Firstly by stars and planets, after by respiration through living beings, mostly in planets. The living bodies, utilizing plasma and mostly gas, are mostly in a liquid crystalline state, sometimes creating solidity, sometimes liquidity, held in tension. With their oily membranes regulating water inside and outside. Color comes in all phases. Mostly in the solidity, but most dull in solidity, earthlike colors. But plasma is bright and vivid, just as crystalline forms of other phases. Color is the main signalling in the visibles. It signals different forms of Life and Death and various tensions. It is no wonders that Ancients mapped chakras with colors. More on this later.&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Electric body sediments or emanates into solid, separate, discrete, extending bodies. This are is what Gnostics called material world and hence tried to escape from, because of its inertness and seeming dullness. But this is an Electric and Sematic blunder. Because, just as there is a degenerated, emanated, cooled, sedimented, coagulated part in Electric route of the crux, there is the Sematic route for degeneration, emanation, cooling, sedimentation, coagulation.&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>After the touching point as actualization (Sematization) and potentialization(Electrification) between potential differences(uniqueness candidates as charge tension) and actual differences(uniqueness candidates as sense tension), system no longer have a touching point. Degeneration as further actualizations (it is in fact, de-actualization, because they pop up as the local system loses energy), happens in two parallel routes. And the sedimented, rigidified part in Sema, turns up as words almost losing their E-S contexts. Thinking is rigidified, unpacked its isolated beginnings and endings, (In circle, beginning and the end is the same.(Heraclitus). In torus, beginning and end is embedded, stacked, dynamic.) it is logicized, and articulated. Articulation of speech does not admit Life, this is completely forgotten by the Gnosticly, or Philosophically inclined. It rather admits slowing down, cooling, ending of the emanation. Here, the colors are grammatical differences. Or the essential, definitive differences. Finitude of Sema and the finitude of the possible “semantic” routes strikes us here. Relations, functions, definitions are sedimented as well. Just as solidified matter is somewhat dead, sematic bodies in this sense are somewhat dead. But in no way, solidity is fully dead. Solid extended bodies, and solid intended bodies, are still have their E-S context, think of a background filamentality, giving them their nutrients, they are charged from outside. Since they are the externalization of the whole within itself as not-whole. They are the part per se. Whole is not its parts, or their sum, but includes them. In two separate attributive aspects, hence, we become dualists if we lose energy.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>But, a worse possibility remains. Both electric solidity and sematic solidity, mapped with cube, hexahedron, by ancients; can be de-contextualized. Since it is the part of the whole which can be teared from its background, is transportable, and mutually exclusive. Possibility for context independence opens the possibility for illusion, simulation, cave-like apparential realm. This is what ancients called appearences, It is the mis-contextual, misdirecting, mischarged aspect of solidity. Thus, solidity has two meanings, in-context, out-of-context. Solidity can be created within itself. Think of it as a cube within a cube. Cave. Indoors. Underground. Being far away from the light and fire of being. Shadow being. But this only shows that, if we are to think in dynamic terms, Solidity can admit three: Organicity(not in the sense of difference between modern chemistry and biology, but in the sense of difference between vitalist bio-chemistry and mechanistic)-analog cubism, inorganicity-mechanistic-digital cubism, and the in-between: the point of interface between analog and digital.&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>The exact analogy is the ancient problem of squaring the circle. Square is the unit of civilization, coming from geurgic spirit, farmlands are of squares. The surface can be tessellated with squares, more importantly three dimensional space can only be tessellated with cubes and non other Platonic solids, elements. Squaring is thus de-contextualizing, discretizing, exclusivizing. Circle is the non-civilized, without any edges, it is of the infinite, it is the context. As instantiated in surface, or sphere in The symbolism, as a Sematic memento, may be this:&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>&lt;image of squaring the circle&gt;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Interfacing shows a transmutative bidirectionality between analog cubism and digital cubism. Square in circle, analog-cubic, may be significant in the same sense that circle in square, digital-cubic, if so, circle is squared. This means, from the context-rigidity, we have exactly one channel, to the context-independent-rigidity. This is exactly what is done in implementing a turing machine. This is important, because most of the problems of civlized security, is related to this interface. “If one dies in the simulative world” in a squaredcircled manner, they might become close to death in an etheric sense as well. But more of that, it is the realm of toxicology. Sometimes what is rigid can kill what is mostly liquid, even if liquid is of more Life than the solid. If it exactly matches the channel, non-living can seem more powerful, and can cause the non-rigid to become rigid. This reversal of power hierarchy, is a form of potentialization, form of rigidification, form of kata-strofe. This occurs in all levels. It is in essence, vulnerability of the spirited. Vulnerability of the living body. Further, it is the possibility for out-of-context-rigidity to be steered from within Life. Life can change the direction of its paths of Death.&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>This will bring the matter into “the residue processes.” before the non-residual processes.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>When energy flows through the system, it forms its pathways, it is either electric or sematic mostly both. This path-ification, is what generates the form and content distinction. E-S touching point, emanates into its residual paths, and forms a feedback loop. (Vernadsky, Peat. hysteresis of an energetic system). Contextualization and decontextualization will have its second meaning here. Residue potentialities (sedimentation of electric) and actualities (sedimentation of sema) becomes identified. Literally, they lost their differential nature, system starts to work with sameness and identity. Sameness is created through the memory of the system, an hysteresis loop.&nbsp; But, again, sameness and identity can be de-contextualized. It can work as an obstacle to further energy, if energical routes become ugly, cancerous, and mis-generative. Paths start to work as paradoxically, it either wastes the energy to fall into unnecessary, unjust vortexes or turbulances. Or it slows it down, it shows non-calibrated inertia. Hence, all the degenerative stasis (both in the sense of inner-war, and in the sense of ) of zombie-like states. Both the rigidity of old age, or the rigidity of ignorance, or the rigidity of mis-intelligence shows exactly this structure. Hopefully, if more energy is passed through the system, this is the upwards part (think of the effects of quinone in the mental states of organism); or if the de-contextualized rigidity, i.e. cancer of soul or of body, is pharmalogically washed down, antidoted (think of the effects of anti-serotonergic substances: “mind expanding.” “outside of box”).</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>These residual processes work as objects. If the primary E-S interface is event-ful, the residuality is object-ful (and hence subject-ful). The left side of the E-S schema is behind the object world. And the right side is where objects are generated, or created. This is exactly a schema of creation, in its full theological sense. Left side etheric, right side chthonic. In the literal sense, Living body has two interfaces, etheric and chthonic, the former is completely vivid, hard to see, but always immediate, energical and significant-sematic–i.e. What an esoteric school may call spiritual. The latter is sedimented, easy to see, but dull, and mediated through energical processes; but works as a ground on which you can step, and which you can use as a stepping stone–i.e. What an esoteric scholl may call material, but the problemacity of this is shown. It is rather, rigidity, solidity, objectivity, externality, exclusivity. To use an Aristotelian term, the realm of secondary potentialities conditioned by prior actualities potentializing, and of secondary actualities conditioned by prior actualities actualizing. They can match, having their context; or they can mis-match. Former works as an acquired skill, working articulation; the latter works as gained non-ignorance working as the obstacle for any further learning, or works as learned-helplessness (the work of Ray Peat exclusively articulates on this, and the relation of it with serotonin, main rigidifier of living body).</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>&nbsp;It is quite interesting that the least powerful aspect of reality can become so forceful in its rigidity and mis-residual inertia. But this is the way “things” are. The power degrees of reality are somehow bidirectional, interdependent, just for the dynamism. Possibility of katastrophe and anastrophe. Realm of change, sedimented into the realm of stasis. And their ouroboric relation, Life, as Living Being(in the realm of change), (sourced etherically, from what is beyond this change) may feed from Death, Death as the coagulation of Life. What is left to mind is not to lose their difference and heterogeneities, while studying the forceful relations between them. And knowing Life is always what is encapsulating in the beginning and in the end. It is the exact glue for every separated and externalized being. It is what make what is potential and what is actual close to each. And if anything works the opposite, it is of Death. We live in mostly close to Death in our living periods, being close to Life is energetic and sematic rareness, works in a pareto law. But, if one tries to become close to Life, whole give the feedback as transmuting the one into a star, enhancing the pareto relation to its broad vicinity.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>&lt;beyond change,&nbsp; change,&nbsp; within change: sameness&gt;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Substance as the background concentric motions, nesting of differentiality creating persistence, exactly related with toroidality and life. – fake substantiality and&nbsp; essentiality, as confusing the right-side illusory rigidity admitting sameness with the left side's powerful ethericity and differentiality. History of philosophy and religion and science&nbsp; is filled with insensitive and irresponsible remarks on confusing exactly this phase-relation. Hence the degenerative idolatry of the degenerative civilization.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Understanding regarding the nature of Life; i.e. the unique in the most peculiar sense, ability to stand in the eye of being, the powerful E-S; is lost by civilization even in its seemingly most fruitful phases. Toroidality is the receptiveness par excellence, it is no wonder both neurons, eye, and all living beings are in the form of torus. It is the law for being the most open part of the whole (straussian, heidegerrian mis-understandings?). Not as an atom, but as the embedding, as the self-sameness. As the golden, or implosive, ratio-nality of self-encapsulation. Only toroid has depth, and has inside and outside differentiated yet in contact. Not the sphere. Sphere is the illusory of the whole within the locality of whole. Any experience of Depth, admits toroidality. Contrast it with un-embedded centrifugality, illusion of depth as the inflating or deflating of ego–extreme activation of HPA axis, dramatism. Contrast with it remembering Dan Winter’s description of zero point energy in many places of his work,&nbsp; life, matter-creating depth, ability to make the still point within a shared, embedded wave, a unique centripetality, a unique vacuum. (Which may be mainstream confused being a black hole. Not at all. Rather, it is the plasmoid, opposite.)&nbsp; This centripetality, relation of ratio-s, and the platonic solids, must be articulated in other entries.&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Un-embedded centrifugality, or an ordinary wave addition, does not admit any Here and There, rather it is a path emanated from a prior locality—it is demonic (Ibn arabi) in the sense of only being of one level, does not have upper and lower fractality, has lower dimensionality. It does not live. But torus always shows and marks its locality, territoriality, just as all living beings. Being in higher dimensionality, at least three, having depth. It is the spirit of Life, and at the same time the spirit of matter. No wonder it is the shape of magnetism, which all existing things have. All toroid feeds from its outside, but at the same time, it creates matter and it ejects energy as beams. (the whole, the infinite, is the sole which is not fed from its outside. Toroid and the whole is interfaced in E-S, in spatiotemporality.) Just the exact pointing of the toroidal attention to some place is “a beam” of the torus, an example is looking. Looking is an exercise, rather exactly it is the non-violent exercise per se, it is a discharge of torus, to be made by E-S it interacts with. Torus mainly interacts with the whole, the other sediments and further phases, works as the appearances, in its last externality, the external parts or the objects works as a veil for closing the E-S touching point.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Especially the human mind, by being the most idolater, wants to be insensitive, forgetful, unthinking, non-acting, and the shifting into the external, sedimented parts is the perfect recipe for non-perception. Humans are prone to live in the cave. Humans are prone to live in the projected object-world of other toroidals, or more unfortunately of&nbsp; non-toroidal non-eyes (any panoptic perspective is not toroidal but externalized and objectified). Back to digital cubism of actual differences, digital cubism of Sema realm. Here, imagination and communication is reversed. Instead of aiming to touch what it tries to visualize (for imagination) or to sign (for communication), it withdraws it to the pointer itself. If it is done artfully, it can be used for a square-circle situation. But, the energetically poor human mind, mostly breaks and fractures when it tries to commit such an act, and gets lost in its representational and non-communicative cave of words. Cave within a cave. This is perhaps the most ugly form of residuality. Residuality of Perception and Thought in cave-mind and hive-mind as the representations and images, without their E-S, vivid, references. “Thought” as energical thrust remains traces in the mind as medium, after that, the traces and the energical event are confused. Only a cancerous study can emerge from such a state, which is what most academical study is about. This residue is what happens exactly in blind or willful ignorance. Secondary potentiality and secondary actuality serving as an obstacle for E-S interface.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>That is why, humans live mostly after the creation. Though creation is multiple, almost infinite, if one lives in such an hive-state, the current creation epoch seems as if solely one and non-changing and the product of the whole, while in fact it is the product of just one toroidality. Confusing the toroidal creation of sedimented objects with god-head's emanation. – This is the ordinary form of anti-heraclitean thinking. “There is nothing new under the sun.” But remembering Velikovskian science, how can one forget even the place of Earth as a planet can suddenly and electrically change in the matter of decades? Forgetfulness is the ordinary state of Humans inability to live in ultimate Change. Creation in its most vivid sense is from the toroidal--the whole is filled with gods who live in tension between them, residing on electrical and on sematical filaments. A god creates worlds, worlds are always in collision. The god, emanates infinitely, making possible a god, the singular toroidal. Polytheistic sense of Strife, correctly accounted in Velikovsky's studies.Mythology is the sedimented and externalized, narrated, form of this tension. In this sense, it is actually, energically, real. But in so far as human becomes insensitive to energy, to actuality, to filamental reality of the torus, it reems as fiction. But in another sence, fictionality is the product of two-dimensional imagination, it is in this sense more real than the concrete objects. Toroidal, zero-point, more real than detoroidal, non-zero-point=vectoral. the tension of at least two vectors being more-like toroidal, is more real than what toroidal produces, projects, and sediments/spurts, as concrete three-dimensional objects. (These are the motions but not the phases of being. More on this in Vortex motion entry. )<br><br>Contrast the human narrow object-intelligence and non-sensitivity with the animal intelligence and sensitivity: An animal is always sensitive to its surroundings. But the human, in its meta-special liquidity, can switch its differential sensitivity as well. But this de-teritorial, de-essential aspect, can easily sediment into fake superiority of what is called human in a short part of evolution, hence warping the not-so-huge distances between animal and human. Rather, it is important to note that human is always animal, and by staying animal, it will transmute itself into further species, but not by staying human.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Toroidal reality is hard to be sensitive of. Most humans in their lifetime could not achieve any further receptivity other than gut feelings, while in fact they study toroidality in their childhood playing and learning: But, more sad than that,, most human do not have any gut feelings left after centrifugal attacks of private and public civilized humans. Mislabeled as education, in adult times tried to be healed by the most ill psychiatry and psychology. Organism must be re-pulled into toroidality. Possibly sublating the veil of external rigidity of soul, through means of liquidifying the soul. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(The sole recomendation of medical doctors of one has to drink such amount of clear water in a day, in a most contrarian way, solidifies, kills the energetic body, it de-spiritualizes the soul, induces a serotonin cascade, de-structures the living water inside organic liquid crystalline body, hence making it loses its child-like turgor, structure, and prone to HPA axis type centrifugal movement. It kills concentric learning, that is why academic crammings include water poisoning. Eccessive non-mineral water drinking not to thrist induces rigidity, suggestability, algorithmization of thinking and playing, and external control. And the serotonin release uncalibrates one as if the water drinking act purifies their medical reality, it gives uncalibrated and absolutizing thinking. This is in no way a katharsis, but a metastasis. One always need more water in such states, causing dependency, and eventually achieving a chronic sub-acute water poisoning, achieving a wet, slimy, pale, and oedematous appearance. Drink fruit or milk instead, with structure, and minerals, and spirit.) <br><br>Yet, this is a matter of constant initiation and re-initiation. This is the Strife in its most general sense.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>&lt;&lt; schema of toroidality within the infinite filamentality, from source, neg-entropic life, and entropic death.<br>? (the One, unknown godhead, infinite in itself,)<br>&gt; 0. filaments, infinite complex existence, as the totality of neg-entropies, chardinian omegapoint's. <br>&gt; 1. two torus: most significant filamentality here. tension in vicinity.<br>&gt; 2. one torus with charging and discharging fields, its internal hole, and its kundalini beam: two polarities<br>&gt; 3. torus no charge but with core and shell, self-veiling, and circle-izing: fruit <br>&gt; 4. circles within circles or circle larger than a square<br>&gt; 4.|5. squared circle or rosicrucian cross : information theory.<br>&gt; 5. inside the box: circle within the square. simulation. cave. object world, created by a torus. not by god. entropic infinite-point as no life present, as non-being. Non-being as Thanatic-serotonergic signal, calibrated, non-being as being, or non-calibrated, non-being as non-being.<br><br>remember: akhenaton dot circle triangle square    or    philosopher's stone<br>remember:  gurdjieffian two triangles as bivalence homogeneous or heterogeneous:<br>from heterogeneity, enneagram and archetypes regarding shelling the bivalence emerges.<br>&gt;&gt;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>? &gt; ETHERIC &gt; TENSIVE-SEDITIVE- &gt; NUTRITIVE &gt; GENETIC &gt; ORGANIC &gt; Int &gt; DIGITAL</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(0) ETHERIC</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Why ether? Why Here and Now? Apart from matter-creation, what is the nature of the creation of Spatio-Temporality, as the medium of toroidal? The simple question can only be answered last.&nbsp;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(1) TENSIVE</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>It is clear that, <strong>at the crux point of experience</strong>, we are re-calibrating the Heraclitean picture into etherical one. At the eye, or at the heart of being, “fire” and “sense”, of life, is intermeshed in its shock-like thrusts and the everchanging vortex movement, embedded and disembedded, having depth and vectoral. The elementality is tetrahedron upon dodecahedron. Living Fire/Sign onto the fabric of the universe. (Remember arrows are triangular, like tetrahedral.) And the implosive, living points, as toroids. But, primacy is in the TENSION, here the law is tension, showing itself as attraction and repulsion. This must not be confused with gravity, because gravity explains it through sedimentations in the system: Upside down causality. Attraction because of mass, reversal of electric understanding. In fact, bodies have mass only because of charge embedding, because of matter-creating power of toroidality. And matter discharging “forcing” (but nonpower) of non-toroidality–repulsion. Spooky action at a distance showing the Godlike’ness of the uniques here. Complete territorial locality shows the animal-like beings of Godlikes. Love and Hate, establishment and war. And the new formings or deformings of toroidality, creating new filamentalities. Always a new contexts for fire and question is re-created. Sublimation and reduction. Transmutation. This is further not exactly about one toroidality. Rather, it is its relation with proximal toroidalities, it is TENSIVE. Daimonic in the sense of it separates itself from its proximal. And it has a boundary to the One. All Living Gods have a proximal boundary to the God above all. And it can endure all colluding and separation. It can endure civil wars, containing the ever possibility of Stasis, Sedition (this will further Sediments rigidified matter, unfortunately).</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(2) NUTRITIVE</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>After the first actualization and the potentialization occurs, we are now in a more “settled down phase.” Mostly pneumatic, between tetrahedron and octahedron. It is about how plasma and gas are related within the toroidal structure of living being. We are dealing with living being more the Life. Life is thrustful and tensive. Living beings are mostly NUTRITIVE. Now, we are not dealing with the changeability of its filamental place. Rather, we accept a filamentality, and study its charge and discharge status. Every God takes its energy from without and give energy to the proximity, it takes, it gives, by doing so, it transmutes. For this, it must be energetically open. For this, it must have its correct toroidal spin: a way to convert outside to inside, and in turn inside to outside: Upwards, and downwards. Earth’s having high energy neutrinos at the South Pole, emanating in the direction of its axis. This is not new or anomalous, clearly every living being is a Reactor, or a Factory (to use Gurdjieff’s term), not in a mechanical but in a transmutative sense. It consumes energy from upwards and transmutes and emits from downwards. Further, it has peripheral local energy. Specially, it also emits as beams, from upwards, and it is charged with a beam from downward. Hence the downsetting of Wilson, or Kundalini awakening. Every part of this movement has ratios. Aura field and the regularities or irregularities also have their ratios. Ancients study this as chakra science. If the ratios or directions are muffled, organism becomes sick. Hence the study of nutritics and hysterics. It is all interdependent. Further, sun systems and social circles resemble each other. Every toroidal proximity can be designed as concentric, but again, remember heliocentric and geocentric problems which one can fall into. But one way or another, this is not changing the reality of auric interfacings&nbsp; between toroidalities. Either in its correct spin and relaxed attentiveness, or in its hysterical and energy stealing modes. Toroidality, and de-toroidality. Former is implosive and Life-Supporting, of Love. Latter is unembedding, unsewing, rusting, Life-taking, of Hate.&nbsp; Most of our pneumatics passes in those interactions. Body forming, deforming, and evolving is due to pneumatic vortex relations. And the Sematic counterpart is not Sema per se, but it is Question. Question mark itself, reminds us the motion is related to toroidality, nutritivity. A question can induce insight, a question can be compassionate and Life-Giving. On the contrary, a question can as well be dis-embedding. Here the matter becomes the various motion types of interacting toruses and their respiratory states. Concentrism and eccentrism starts to emerge. Auto-motivation and allo-motivation.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Oxidation and respiration inextricably linked in the Reactor, the Factory, of torus. Just as this, the formulated questions act like breathing in the mind, they are what motivates the mind to further study. For the attention to delve into circular motions around its uniques. Sema as the charge-sense-meaning depth, and the question as the receptacle for inhaling and exhaling, and the further shape, frequency, vibration of breathing. If there is no question, there would not be living being. If there is a mis-question, cutting the torus open, there would be a quickly dying living being, wasting in the process. Charge bleeding and sense bleeding is the degenerative aspects of this phase. From a pneumatic wound, spirit escapes, both electrically and sematically.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(3) GENETIC</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Towards residual processes and objectification, toroidality starts to be veiled. An openness to infinitude wanes both for the looking eye and for the seen’s, as if the eye is also veiling its surface sensation, sedimented into pre-givens. Here, the depth of Life gives its place to pre-set originals and their further generations. Think of a torus starting to create a shell around itself, and a core within itself; trying to act like a sphere. It exactly seems like a sphere from the outside. Precisely because of this, a real sphere does not exist in nature, but every being takes the form of a sphere. (This shell-core creation in its literal sense occurs both in stars, planets, and in fruits, as well as all living beings.) Shell-like and chtonic is of almost the same meaning. Shelling is what makes possible any cubic residue to hold on. We are between pneuma and liquid, remembering the beginning of life as a oxidative power pneumatically shaped, found its oily membrane as its shell. First, liquidity becomes the shell for pneuma, then membranes come. Having its outermost membrane, the toroidal separates its inward and outward and can completely isolate its inner world from outside. This will bring the appearance of immunity from outside world, a godlike appearance. And if other spherelike cells are pneumatically less powerful than the one in question, then the genetical process begins. Mimetics and memetics of the generation of toroidality begins. In the sense that a toroidal can start a chainlike phenomena among others, that is, if it can be the center of a concentric wave-like motion, it self perpetuates through others. It lives in others. Until now, we have graph-like relations between toroidality, but now, this is the possibility of tree-like hierarchy. Thus, essentiality. Exactly this processes starts the organic hierarchy of bodies, electrically. Electrically, some processes are more centrifugally important in bodies. And further, in the sense of a stacked vortex movements, this relation brings substance property relation, exactly one changing motion is more pneumatically-vortically enduring than others to the point that outside eye looking at it can say that substance endures.&nbsp; Or in Sema, insight and intuition have this centripetal power over what changes. Again, form and content relation emerges in this residuality phase. And the foremost, conceptuality emerges, which can be thought as macro Electric and Sematic harmonic relations between micro scale movements of uniques.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Genetics is necessary in the phases, but it is what starts the illusion. Publicity and privacy in toroidality, becomes to be distributed and decontextualized. Exactly this de-contextualization, brings the everyday dualism, externality, object-level-understanding, and most importantly, uni-valence thinking. that is to say, when transitioning from bivalence to univalence, bodies and ideas are started to be compared with regard to one given criteria; it is as if some bodiese become the paradigm for other bodies. and formality and paradigmality, originality, veils itself from within the system, shows as if from without. Transcendence emerges, comcomitantly with the shelling and oblivion of the toroidal. Bivalence which is inherent in all hot life, i.e. all directions having at least two, and actually infinite, non-zero vectoralities; and which is always in a context, started to become unfolded to its two counterparts, and one part becomes object-level, and other is lost within a shadow realm. And only one non-zero valence, started to act like the criteria. This is the start of Paranoid-Schizoid thinking: a vine has always curved motion, in a tension of multiple, at least two, non-zero directionality when growing, due to the necessary motion of the relevant star and relevant planet, of a light and of a soil; if it is under light and rooted in soil. But, if one isolates the growing vine from its light and soil; then one can inspect all its branches and root-branches under perfect univalent hierarchy; but this comes with a price, the price of losing the etheric, the vivid. All paranoid-schizoid works in a dualist fashion by seperating what is most, from more or less. This brings organicity and human realm, a possibility for filtering membranes, according to parameters: a possibility for articulation, and for boundaries to become isolated from what is bounded. Most of PS part works as a byproduct, relating that we are still in a non-solid realm, but only having to give the possbility of mimetics and genetics. genes and memes, while being distributed from one body to another, works as unchanging and comparable bodies. We are not yet in the realm of complete PS. We have still roots in soil, but, the isolatability criteria is given.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(4) ORGANIC</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Between the liquid and the solid, organic body of the living resides. This is the part for the permeability and semipermeability of the cellular stages. After a form content relation and the living substantiality is formed, further articulation regarding tissue and membranes, variety of difference in intensity, brings forth liquid-liquid and liquid-solid relations within the body. Being oil-like and water-like, or polarity becomes important. For the Sema, mostly we are in the realm of logical flows between sematic, semantic components of sensible parts, we are in the grammar. Loose or strict definitions. Relations between names, definiton, essentialities, logical relations, being able to be isolated from their uttered contexts.&nbsp; And working as living by themselves.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>… &lt;to be articulated&gt;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(4) | (5). square circle and the chtonic surface.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Discretization and digitalization.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(5) MECHANIC-DIGITAL</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>After the discretization occurs. Realm of opinions, no form content thinking, only with a shallow univalence and hidden-governing PS. Let alone the etheric or tensive or nutritive context; genetic and organic contexts are also lost in translation. To the point that any discussion on the existence of any context itself is subjected to de-contextualization as a threat to mass or private hypnosis. That is to say, hypnoic mis and displacement of electrical power and sematic power cannot be discussed and every object must be treated as if in itself. While inf fact translation to digitality always comes with an angle of dis- and mis-placements. (This angle is an absent residue of resiualization processes. Only a forensic etherical investigation can found this, as the real error in externalization, toroidal genesis, world-within-world (or cave/simulation/"matrix") forming.) The trance-like hypnotic state (Gurdjieff, Roy Masters) of all people, either falling into public PS of their sect, or living into PS shared space of their private sects. Hypnosis governs all, in either a state of minor depression or hypomania. The former is of the casuality of the city, its occupations, professionalisms and everyday polemicism. The latter is of the manipulativity of the city or of the local cult, it is breadcrumbed by manipulative energetic-regulators veiled as saviours. Hypomanicity is opinionated by the regulators; the dosage musst be controlled in such a pharmakon forming act. By making the mass forgetful to those two: (a) Medicine in various dosages can be turned into posion. (b) medicine and nutrient is different. (c) nutritivity and regeneration is not possible, hence one must completely embrace the given medicine as absolute pharmakon. The latter hypnotics is what forms the authority, and always fuel and control the energetic vortex motion in civilized bodies in city or in private groups. This is why city needs entertainment, which is in fact entrainment and acousmatics-musics, to use a Neuro Linguistic Programming and Pythagorean or a Platonic term.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>The latter hypomanics (and not minor depresiveness) is a much more violent hypnosis, and mostly called "gaslightling" or "cult formation" by the former, because it mostly destructs ego functions of the individual organism by inflating and estaticizing the ego, contary to public minor-depressive PS which is exactly designed to maintain the organic ego functions of various occupations which exist in a city simultaneously, while allowing the private world of professionals is maintained somewhat more smoothly and less rigidly. Private PS in a city is the  mirror image of public PS. And must be in the city in a correct ratio--The cybernetic forcing of minor depressive forces over hypomanic forces must be called regulation of "controlled opposition," which must include intricate cybernetic intermeshing of various PS creators and skilled degeneratives whom most would call psychopaths. This dual forcing between degenerative forces veils the real war between what is etherically transmutative and chtonic representatives of absolute transmutation. Hypomanics and minor-depressives both create each other, and this exact feedback relation itself globally showing the "sickness" of the residual established body. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(Forensically, can show what went wrong in the regenerative act of establisment, establishment as a process and not residue.) (And please be careful, every regenerative can fall into such degenerative forcing battle, since every zero-point can be bled to the point of degenerative inflation and to the point of losing the etheric calibration. This is what happens to most sovereign canditates having decent insight but eventually losing their ethericity through various stressing factors throughout their publicity.) </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>The filters created by both act like a narrowing-filter for vision, only some objects, rigid and solid, can be seen. Possibility of new object formation, or even seeing an object's morphic structure is impossible. Depth in the surface of vision is lost. All objects and the corresponding subjects are pre-determined, sedimented, coagulated. Only think left is do commit the triggered and algorithmized centrifugal motion as the local technics, or the local drama of public and private PS. And this is why, anti-depressants, hence serotonin, always fuels the public and private establishments, by enforcing the veil over all other more-energetic phases, and by maintaining minor-depressive states preventing them being fall into complete depression and bounce back as uncontrollable manics. Mostly, minor-depressive takes the burden of ego-function for the regulators-hypomanics, both public and private. In some sense, city can only be mechanically maintained by the elbow grease and constant plumbing-maintenance of professionals-technicians; intermittenttly fueled by a manic content, in their home when their plumbing work is done. this relation is a degenerative caricature of shamans communicating with ancestors, gods, spirits. Shamans sensitive to infinitude are mostly outnumbered by hypomanics as the savior-opposition, which are regulatively veiled by hypomanics as elite, which are veiled by the forcing and imperfect motion sedimenting of all minor-depressive processes together. And system in its various doxic chambers hold in tension various discordant parts distant enough so that no global explosion as an existential threat to "estanblished-machine" can occur. This works although no all-encompassing cybernetic power existent (assuming the contrary is to fall into error of monopolizing all forces, and hence confusing power with force, and projecting forces as an absolute one frind or enemy.) This works through the tensive stability of various forcing vectors, and this is mostly veiled by PS-thinking, monopolizing friend and enemies within the all echo-chambers circles of the city-body.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Do not confuse a real transmutative and creative esotericism with an hypomania-regulating-authoritarianism. A real school is not scholastic. It is not hyperverbal, but experiential. Always works in tension and in interfacing and in touch, not in word. A real meaning and electricity, hence daimonics and ethics, of a possible esotericism must be determined here. Real power of real knowledge, always is Grown in a springs of existences and not it the mainstream, within mostly child-like thinking, and conserving what is most sensitive to outside forcings. It has fractality and embedding, forceful Decays will over-excite it hence spoil it. Child-like thinking and playing cannot be forcefully spoiled. High metabolism, which is the only metabolism which can study the minute differentials of life as Growth and Decay, must be conserved by all means, no matter what is needed. This would be in two channels: Nutritive and tensive. By regulating correct charge into correct place. Seeding correct soil with correct initial conditions. This conservation and conversation itself works with Growth and Decay, and must always be on the side of further Growth; by constantly calibrating on where the Decayed lies within or without.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>… &lt;to be articulated&gt;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Most people are in the realm of (5), in the most degenerative part of it, working only in possession, opinionated but does not know how opinions formed from torus to the digitality. Complete loss regarding states/phases of matter and spirit, loss of elementality, and forgetfulness of the toroidal, electric and sematic, or who they really are. Falling into false-self conceptions, privately or publicly created, injected, entrained from without.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Esoteric tradition emphasizes initiation and not to give sensitive information to the non-initiated. They are both right, and wrong. Initiation is always possible and not a discrete process. In fact, childs are almost initiated, remembering, without de-toroidal wounds upsetted constantly. But, initiation is from the upset and catabolic and insensitive adult position into the next and energetic version of oneself. In that sense, initiation may be of a life thing, and have its discrete turning points, and cannot easily induced externally and uncarefully. The real knowledge by all means must be preserved in safe places. And any stepping stone, is of value, and again, must be shown to others, phase by phase. Not just at once. Both electrically and sematically,the&nbsp; individual must be challenged and not be manually fed. Start from what is most rigid, since this is what veils the soul. Start from serotonin, via Peat, what is the rigidifier of Soul.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>End in E-S. But, this not a real end, rather, the real life starts Here and Now, in E-S. All other is the veiling of toroidality, nutritivity, tension, and ethericity. Real life starts here, to ask the most intriguing “Why?” Why Here and Now, I am? This, along with the energetic thrusts of E-S, i.e. staying and living in Change, is hard to endure. But, if soul can stand still in the beauty and brutality of the fire of being, eye of being, the sign; if it can achieve to embed by being in the correct place, Here&amp;Now, with a correct attitude, to encapsulate its pain, charge and sense bleeding, then, it does not delve into Death, but discovers the further Life in question. High energy, in that way, does not burn the living body, contrary to it, high energy sublimates the living body. With a pure sense, and pure heart. This is what heals, and this is what opens the possibility of new toroidality, new life. This comes in both pleasure and pain, in its new forms. And this is what exactly we call Courage, or "Daring to Truth," to use an "enlightenment" term. And in contrary, impure heart and disembedding, make one's energical body is a fuel for external sublimating processes: The body literally burns up if it does not achieve to find the way "to embed," in the correct place, when the new fire of being comes. "Wasting to the bone." This process exactly occurs both in species level de-toxification and immunization, and in public or private matters of human life. (Macro scale of such phenomena is no different than a catastrophist mega-fauna extinction with a solar flare (an extremely hot visible-fire) and/or a pole shift (sudden eccentricity of the toroidal taxis). Or than a mythical-spiritual depiction of a dimensional change.) In that option of burning of the body and of the mind, toroidality is still existent. But it is not the toroidality of Here and Now, but There and Thence. Center of Energical body and center of torus is not coinciding but only juxtaposed. So not a zero point, but a Vector-like force, de-energy, non-zero point. SO the Vector emerges. Forceful. External locus is in its motion, an imperfect motion. This is the case of not being able to be correctly present at the wake of the current E-S. In accordance to the Natural combustion, body is pierced, "spirit" flies away, to some other place. This Life becomes the matter for another distant Life. Life continues, but with fewer bodies. (Ray Peat) Fewer, exactly because of matter-pulling and matter-creating embedding is lost. Both literal Death, and metaphorical Death occurs in this way. Remember alchemical Putrefactio, or Nigredo. But, Hope is the most enacapsulating. And new toroidality always comes after a destruction, either this Now, or one of the other Now's. Re-generative law is the one above all. And the etherization of the body's liquid matter (Steiner) is the aim for further Life. Starting with anti-serotonin=anti-solidity, continuing with implosive-centripetal nutritive interventions=ethericity-&gt;plasmicity-&gt;pneumaticity: Electron acceptability=charge capacity=toroidality of body must be enhanced: through full spectrum incandescent red light, CO2, calcium, thyroid, progesterone, quinones(vitamin koagulation and menaquinones as charge acceptors of bones&amp;tissues, cascara as the charge accepting for intestine), copper, fructose, glucose oxidation, saturated fats (Peat).</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Two important things to further research into this blogs are the above paragraphs. Un-calibrated solidity act like cancerous emanation diverged from the infinite even if it comes from it. It acts like a False representation of God, so to speak with <strong>the </strong>gnostic term per se. False Ground blocks the way to what is Etheric, to what is Energical. A downward block to the what is infinite. (This is exactly why Stars have mega-flares succesfully sweeps all chtonic residuality in planets. This acts like a filter, evaluating who has etheric intelligence and hence is a candidate for next generation of organisms. Spore-like formations of knowledge can persist biggest catastrophes, this is the aim of real science. Knowledge as a meta-toroidal meta-biological structure will be finely attended in future entries.) Similarly, Attention always is fed by the etheric energy. If the etheric "acceptors" are poor materially, if attention cannot receive its "primary matter," both in its most "literal", most "etheric", and most scholastic sense; then the organism de-tunes from the infinite source. The importance of Ray Peat is vital here, anti-serotonergical substances exactly dissolves the uncalibrated residual solidity. And the pro-respiratory bio-energetic ones exactly the ones accepts the etheric energy. Latter is the Upward part. The former is the Downward. The enablings of which is experienced through the correct spins in the vortex movement of Chakras of the Toroid. The toroidal spin is corrected, from Up to Down. This two give the hope and a responsibility to us to regenerate. This responsibility is not only Nutritive but also Tensive. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>This is a two-sided strategy to be sensitive, to be thoughtful, to stay growing, and to stay grounded. Exactly by studying the Pathos of Life. (Theosophist school may not be wrong when ascertaining the three faculties as Head, Hand and Heart. Here is almost the same: Sematic, Electric, Pathetic. The last seems to be related to the alignment of the two. Words and Deeds. This intricate relation of the last with the former two is to be investigated later.) Unfortunately,and fortunately, Pathos comes both in its positivity and negativity. But remember that the Positive always encapsulates the Negative. This is the principle which always arises in one guise or another at the beginnings of Philosophy, e.g. Ancient beginnings or phenomenological "Meditations," or at the re-energizings of Science, as if it is the regenerator of a sick tradition, or the suspender of natural attitude. There is a vivid "place" which all beings, even and foremost, the Falsity (or say Non-Being), is Given as encapsulated by the Truth, as "in" True. This is the tapping and the tuning into the infinite source, of what is finite. This is to be in touch with Infinite, even if the Attentive Organism itself is finite. It has an Etheric Boundary to the Unbounded, Attention, filtered Electric and Sematic, just because it is the Toroidal, being one among infinite Gods. First filamentally in the general sense, then mentally and matterly filamentally in the local senses, connected to the God above all. Always Here and Now. Present and not admitting Death. That is to say, in no way can it be destroyed by any, other than the infinite itself. <br><br>And it is important to note that, here, not just the words but to the energetics itself must point to the infinite source, in contrary to almost all philosophical scholasticism and hyperverbalism. Demonstration always is not verbal but Electric and Sematic. It is not a deduction but a discovery, and induction; an internalization of a new insight, calibrating Hand and Head, thus of Heart. (The movement is no different then the psychoanalytic Insight. the movement of discovery is not diffent than "healing.") Discovery always is about the feeling, at the interface with the infinite. It comes from experimentation and self-experimentation and not from discourse or from instruction. Both from electric experimentation and sematic experimentation, subjecting one's self to higher energies and higher meanings through literal Fire and Question. And to the intricate bi-directional causality between the two. Sometimes the Fire ignites a Question, some other times the Question ignites a Fire. (And the causality needs its own place in the future entries.) Study of truth cannot be separated by study of metabolism. A school can and must study its own metabolism and its own toroidality, then its filamentality, or else, it becomes "scholastic." And hyperverbalism or over-discretizing attitude itself is prone to two-sided error depicted above, of Upward and Downward. Unless the scientist study its own self, their organism becomes veiled from Etheric, Tensive, Nutritive, and mostly from Genetic phases, because they lose themselves and lose their Change with respect to themselves, lacking Self-Knowledge, on how the exact structure, or the exact terminology, is gained its electricity and its meaning.  This is a perfect recipe for a Self-absorbed science hence non-science. Non-science can only study sedimentations of the Vortical Change as the samenesses. Non-science cannot be present at he thrustfulness of Vortex movement. It is not intelligent and powerful enough to stay in the realm of Change. Hence possiblity of a self-change, rejuvenation, is lost, there no new Event or Process in the whole, only objects and results.<br><br>Thus any initiation, if any, works backwards, from Digital, to Organic, to Genetic, only after the experience of those, to the Toroidal and to the Tensive. And it is always of vortically moved, always thrusted into re-initiation moments, always lost in the course of life, and re-gained through Upward and Downward interventions. Do not lose your spirit. Spirit can escape anytime from the de-toroidal punctures in energical body, i.e. from the wounded-inflamede body; if seemingly "awake" (but mostly hypnotic, if not psychotic) time is passed "detuned." If unfruitful catabolism is inevitable, sleep, form spores, hibernate, chant, but do not be uncontrollably exposed to uncalibrating centrifugality. Be aware of what you permit yourself to be exposed of, be aware of your E-S content regarding Here and Now, be careful where you look at, be careful what you visualize-imagine. The need for sleep and for dream, of all organisms including planets and stars, is exactly this. More on awake-dreaming or lucid-dreaming or sleep as internal control (in contrast to hypnotic entrained states which is induced by external locus of control) later in further entries.<br><br>Real Science is pathetic. But, do not underestimate the pure pleasures of Life, seeing and feeling the pure Electrics, and looking at the pure Signs, of Life. Vivid, colorful. Mostly Living is cheerful. Some other critical times, one has to bear ones own core Agony, but only the most significant Agony, not all, in order to grow. It must be "yours." In both, the embedding of vortical energy must be preserved in a tensive way, i.e. in a tension. Either through known, or unknown embeddings, known or unknown toroidalities whose center points are exactly here and now. Or else, the living in question explodes, hence become dead. Most what is called science nowadays is dead and post-apocalyptic, in an isolated way. In their isolated containers, decayed and expired: not able to study its own projections, its own objects, i.e. its own explosion.<br><br>Growth, as the most akin to Truth (Peat, citing Reich, in Generative Energy), works by regenerating and by embedding all wounds in its proximity and locality, even the Decay (Falsity or Fragmentation or Disembedding) itself. <br><br>And there is no upper limit to energize. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>&lt;vortexes toward each other&gt;</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>14</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-02 05:06:11</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-02 02:06:11</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-18 01:05:24</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-17 22:05:24</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>crux-point-of-experience</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>1</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[s:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1673993130]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80164571576]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1672625174]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Tension of implosive self and explosive self. Winnicott's true self and false self. Complexes.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/04/tension-of-implosive-self-and-explosive-self-winnicott-complexes/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 19:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=101</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><em>Ordinary self as fractured. Circular motion in psyche. Complexes as uni-valent filters, solidifying. Psyche and self as the fractality and embedding of various, liquid, vibratory filterings which can mutate and transmutate in the sense of phase-change. Extreme Solidities: borderline and psychotic uni-filtering of information. Inflation of soul. Vortex physics of psyche. Explosion points, system theory. Heart as cardioid curve. Tension between heart and explosive abysslike de-focal points of soul. Winnicott's shell analogy. Empty shell, empty core of object theory. Science of hysteria, as seperating the third from the sick de-toroidal second, embracing the second.  Third as the explosive points in psyche. Relation of explosiveness and wound-making. Wounds in the energical body as enlargable and shrinkable, in contrast to victim dual mentality as endlessly projective and responsibility-injective. Ordinary animalic mode of wound healing and smooth distancing to the wounded while healing.</em></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>101</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-04 22:54:57</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-04 19:54:57</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-06 22:00:40</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-06 19:00:40</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>tension-of-implosive-self-and-explosive-self-winnicott-complexes</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1672862099]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80247876904]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[u:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1673031643]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Seven layers of causality with respect to oblivion of toroidality. Mis-causal triggering automata.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/04/seven-layers-of-causality-with-respect-to-oblivion-of-toroidality-mis-causal-triggering-automata/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 20:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=111</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><em>Akahshic-etheric causing the tensive: god realm causing the spatio-temporal tensive realm. Electric causing Sema. Sema causing Electric. <br>Electric causeing. Plasma causing Pneuma. Pneuma-&gt;Liquidity. Liquid-&gt;analog solidity. Solid-&gt;Leak-&gt;Meta-solid distributable.<br>Sema causing Sense. Sense-&gt;Question. Question-&gt;Insight/Induction/Discovery. Insight-&gt;Deduction, Definition, Relation. Essentiality. Logics-&gt;Leak-&gt;Opinions, Representations, Images.</em><br><em>Parallelistic causation and Spinoza. Miscausation, as (1) between solid extended distributed bodies, as (2) between ideas, opinions, representations, images. Miscausal chains as the veiling of the real. Syncronicity as the real causality.</em></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>111</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-04 23:02:29</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-04 20:02:29</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-04 23:02:29</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-04 20:02:29</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>seven-layers-of-causality-with-respect-to-oblivion-of-toroidality-mis-causal-triggering-automata</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80248052284]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1672862551]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[s:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1672862723]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Faculty of Visualization, Imagination, of Willing. Relation to Serotonin. Awake dreaming in contrast to asleep nightmaring, or hypnotic states.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/04/faculty-of-visualization-related-to-will-awake-dreaming/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 20:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=116</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><em>Everyone visualizes, either knowing or unknowing. Tradition of Neville Godard, Genevieve Behrand. Internal visualization as very minimal framing of what is to be happen, and not more. The work is always made on the go, interfaced with fate. Wanting of what is though impossible, and ready for catastrophe, as the learner. --- External visualization is of the exploding serotonergical cascade, either by endotoxicity, or by irritation. Serotonin, in all dosages, induces visualization. Positive visualization is also serotonergical, but non-exploding differentially, and it is of miniscule amounts: What people call motivation. It is of visualization because it gives the trajectory for solidification processes, hence, the creative power of the toroidal. God creates only the filamentality, primary non-God as the ether. Torus, the zero-point bottleneck between the filamentalities, creates objects: Genetic power is of torus. Anti-serotonergical substances of the resetters of what is experience as solid, as objects. Hence, giving new possiblities of object generation. Serotonin, in controlled amounts, always comes. Hence, objects, solidity, always come. Peat's alchemical recipe for object transmutation: awake dreaming. Remembering the dream thought from its last point, "filaments of imagination." Relation of dreams to the galactic filamentality. Do God's dream?  Closed eye visuals as the beginning of visible: rendering the invisible visible.  "Thought Forms" of Besant and Leadbeater, Kandinsky, af Klint, Klee, and others. -- Contrarily: those who are not succesful at positive visualization, always de-lucidifies their dream in a tragical unfolding of the what is prophecy-like, exactly while escaping and self-fulfilling. They cannot dream, they nightmare. Anti-lucid nightmaring, as the anti-ergonomic hypnosis. Negative anima, vacuuming of life energy. Absence of positive visualizaiton. Only negative, and the negation of the negative. Its serotonergy always reacts, and re-reacts; hence, explosion of external locus of control. A tragic hypnosis and non-dreamability of mind. In contrast, a quite articulated image of happiness comes in such negative states: Serotonin cascade as "the responsible." A wastage of libidinal power, hence, fulfilled as inverted or perverted sexuality: Blocks in the internal-helix structure, chakras, of the energical body  Those who cannot pull the energy downward, cannot make kundalini: A sequence of awakenings. Relation of thin poetic beam to the extensive pulling of charge of a torus. Reich. Christ with in as sacred secretion, claustrum: the cerebrospinal superfluid, etherization. Just as planets make oil, all toroidal makes oil for kundalini. Poiesis and nutritivity/pathos. Intensities and extensities of organism. Deleuze's "of the refrain." The vivid music of simply existing, and entrainment or neuro-linguistic programming as the hive-mind-ing processes, waswas. Why animals sing? Chanting. Relation between singing and logos. Logos and problematization. Problems are not spoken of, the problems are those who speaks.</em> Dissolving the problem, and euphoric .re-problematization, as the alchemy. --- Pulsars: obstacle projecting, being enemy with its own sedimentation processes, referring "electrically stressed selective attention." Gnostic anti-materialism. In contrast, alchemical transmutation of the obstacle into a stepping stone. "Squaring the circle" as the symbol of anti-serotonergical serotonergy, anti-solid solidity. Rosicrucian cross symbol as the squaring of the circle. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>116</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-04 23:03:48</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-04 20:03:48</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-09 03:24:14</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-09 00:24:14</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>faculty-of-visualization-related-to-will-awake-dreaming</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80248084332]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[s:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1673223860]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Facing with Reality. Schizoid, Borderline, Anti-Schizoid escapes. Vortex genetics of trauma, gradual fragmentations of soul. Empty Core as the filter between.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/04/facing-with-reality-schizoid-borderline-anti-schizoid/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 20:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=118</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Misgeneration and perversion of visualization function in post infancy ages, resulted from the excessive attention to negative visualization. Losing the ability to dream, curiously veiling itself as being prone to excessive daydreaming. Fragmentation of libidinal energy, and sucking points. Three sequential defenses of withdrawal from life in infancy. And the resulting  hysterical problems in energetic body. Relation of three stages to Life and Death. Being already dead in Fear of Death. Vaknin's genetics, and problems. Provisional life, fear of living, and depth psychology. Jung, von-Franz. Vampirism with regard to dreams. Scizo and anti-schizo as a tensive contrast. developmental perspectives. Three energetic vacuum points with regard to anabolism and catabolism. waste of energy in a general perspective to civilization, public and private PS-injections. Attention vacuums and explosion points. Suppression of upward moving beam-energy in body, or the external control of it, external sublimations as politics. Re-gaining the generative/imaginative/visualization power, with regard to seperation and individuation from "prote ergo obligo." Play as the channelling of libido the Reality, enough, minimal, internal visualization, place of Love and real Anger.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Mind-blindness, or solipsism. Developmental stages starting with autism, schizoid, anti-schizoid. Empathy. Relation of it to chronic serotonin syndromes in either fetal or infantile states.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>118</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-04 23:16:27</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-04 20:16:27</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-05 22:20:48</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-05 19:20:48</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>facing-with-reality-schizoid-borderline-anti-schizoid</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80248390206]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1672863389]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[u:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1672946451]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Wastage as a trickster: anti-functional somatizations as Sema to the tribe of Toroidals.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/05/trickster-anti-function-somatizations-as-sema-to-the-tribe-of-toroidals/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 21:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=134</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Cancerous points in a body of local filamentality and their significance to that locality.  Excessive rigidifation of ordinary ego functions. Degeneration and misgeneration as mirror images. Sema always points to the new toroidality. Shit-tests and double-binds, public and private. Rigidity of ethos, creates a cancerous point as anti-ethical and antithetical. Analogies to astronomic bodies: quasars, twin stars, catacylismic variable star. Role of wastage in bigger picture since energy always goes somewher, especially in explosive non-zero points. vectorality of wastage as a special Sema.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>134</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-05 00:12:32</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-04 21:12:32</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-05 00:28:20</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-04 21:28:20</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>trickster-anti-function-somatizations-as-sema-to-the-tribe-of-toroidals</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[s:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1672867704]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80249602766]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1672866755]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Katharsis as healing, metastasis as re-traumatization veiled as absolute health.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/05/katharsis-as-healing-metastasis-as-re-traumatization-veiled-as-absolute-health/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 22:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=144</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>144</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-05 01:34:27</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-04 22:34:27</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-05 01:34:27</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-04 22:34:27</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>katharsis-as-healing-metastasis-as-re-traumatization-veiled-as-absolute-health</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80251302368]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[s:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1672871832]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Disembedding of a negentropical stack, as a sema of Thanatos, as history, relevant past. Role of Serotonin, in so far as non-local. Akashic records. Three serotonergies.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/06/disembedding-of-a-negentropical-stack-as-a-sema-of-thanatos-as-history-relevant-past-role-of-serotonin-in-so-far-as-non-local-akashic-records/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 16:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=153</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Imprinting of the past and somewhat future, always admits Death. Past is more Death-like than the future. One is Decay, other as possible Growth as a Decay (negative visualization). Positive visualization of a minimal death trajectory later to be regenerated. Space imprinting as somatization. Time imprinting and identities of self-states, broken heart as a geometrical psychic phenomena. Relation of time imprinting to space imprinting. Imprinting, traces and representations relates to PS, a residue of "bivalence." Difference of history, memory and the experience of time passing. Time experience in serotonergic and anti-serotonergic states. Serotonin as the sequencing mediator per se. Inflated attention and narrow cause-effect chains, example of "pandemic:" Not being able to forget, and that PS overflows the memory, switching of self-states. A possiblity of sequencing of sequences: Death trajectories.  Relation of it the Akashic or Etheric records. Reincarnation, memory as a content of spooky action at a distance. Memory as matter in Ether, infinite possible memory layers in implosive states of living, brain as a filtering device being a residue-filter (Huxley, Peat), relation to Bergson's theory. Seperation-individuation phase of infants as a local identity sedimentation. Real and false meaning of Identity, dynamic and static. Blood as fluid, as a superfluid, and in contrast as coagulated, three states of heart, geometric representations. Coagulated blood and unilayerings of memory. Unilayer and identity as given, not the Self but the self-"state." Three serotonergies: infant &gt; child &gt; adult &gt; elder. Convex concave life's, Rosicrucian concept. Three individuations. Life as a bridge phenomena. A new meaning of esotericism, via Peat. Four stages of toroidality, of Life, naive concentrism, naive eccantrism, real concentrism, real eccentrism(with respect to the infinitude as one, among infinite infinities)---and the vortex relations of the four. Real meaning of education, as the Living communication between third and fourth stages, talk of the golden child and golden elder. Global serotonergy giving the possiblity to study beyond experience: sequencing of Here and Now's, Ouspenskii's study of Kant's forms of experience. Is the question "Does God dies into Toroidal?" meaningful, or E-S? How beyond-change, beyond-spatiotemporality, nonHere and nonNow, eternity, communicates with locality?</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>153</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-06 19:23:47</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-06 16:23:47</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-07 03:46:40</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-07 00:46:40</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>disembedding-of-a-negentropical-stack-as-a-sema-of-thanatos-as-history-relevant-past-role-of-serotonin-in-so-far-as-non-local-akashic-records</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80304843884]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[s:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1673052404]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Anti-toroidal. Non implosive Vacuum in general,  Psychic and Political implications. Stasiology as a (ek)central science. Vortex relations of (s,  b, a-s) anti-toroidalities. What fuels the Polis?]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/06/anti-toroidal-non-implosive-vacuum-in-general-psychic-and-politic-implications-stasiology-as-a-ekcentral-science-vortex-relations-of-s-b-a-s-anti-toroidalities-what-endures-human-city/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 18:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=168</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Dion Fortune. Toroidality and anti-toroidality, downsetting and upsetting. Upset and pole-shift phenomena, galactic and social catastophies as a interdependence between star, planets and satellites. Jeffrey Seinfeld. Klein bottle as the analogy. Zero point and vector, and three dimensionality, Ibn arabi. Geometry and stasiology, and the three-dimensionality as the tension between Etheric and Genetic. Currency in a most general sense. Blood as the most distributed currency: tension between copper and iron, sun-energy, world-energy, plasma and magma. Centralization versus de-centralization. Ethos and daimonics, Heraclitus. Tension between Christ spirit and Jihad spirit. Meaning of Straussian Platonic esotericism, relation of Politics and Ontology. Justice with respect to Human and God--Heraclitus. Justness. Of Definitions, of Names, of essences. Attention as Godlike, attention-vacuum vectors as the God-representations. Content of Here&amp;Now. Currents of attention, and currency: Real essence of capital, mapped to the movements of Attention, whose potentialities and actualities.  Relation of justice and genetics. Role of serotonin regulation, critical philosophies. Socrates, as a twofold figure. Paleolithic era and civilization, growth and decay. Polis and cities. Community as a toroidal having an imploded currency in tension---in contrast to flock regulated with sense-vacuum, inflation of sense and of capital. Implosive and explosive economy, relation of it to "daimonics."  System theory, attraction and repulsion, relation of it to harmonics, overtones of currency.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>168</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-06 21:40:25</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-06 18:40:25</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-06 22:07:14</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-06 19:07:14</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>anti-toroidal-non-implosive-vacuum-in-general-psychic-and-politic-implications-stasiology-as-a-ekcentral-science-vortex-relations-of-s-b-a-s-anti-toroidalities-what-endures-human-city</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[u:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1673032037]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1673030427]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80308138089]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Vortex motion as natural motion, centripetal and centrifugal. Two cones. Perfect motion, concentric, as stacking of vortices: zero point. Imperfect as non-zero point, vectorality, non-natural motion.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/07/vortex-motion-as-natural-motion-centripetal-and-centrifugal-two-cones-perfect-motion-concentric-as-stacking-of-vortices-zero-point-imperfect-as-non-zero-point-vectorality-non-natural-motion/</link>
  <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 23:22:45 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=188</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Vortex mathematics/physics and vectoral algebra as an analog and dijital counterparts, and the possible interfacings between them. Daimonics in contrast to demonics, Ibn Arabi. Caduceus, phase conjugation, golden ratio of Dan Winter. Implosive points and explosive points. Heart/embryso, cord to explosive point. Walter Russell, harmonics, cones and starting of mathematics. Micro natural motion and macro natural motion, nestings of helices as forward or backward, or upward or downward. Anastrophe and catastrophe, strophe in general. Analogues in Astronomy and Biology, Birkeland Currents, DNA. Filamentality and vortices, tension in general. Non-natural demonics as the external perspective of natural motion, mirror-images, projective geometry. Relation of vortex and harmonics to torus. Most general mathematics.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>ibn arabi, daimonics and demonics, and four motions of being:<br></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:list {"ordered":true} -->
<ol><!-- wp:list-item -->
<li>perfect motion as zero-point embedding energy, daimonic relation with the whole.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item -->

<!-- wp:list-item -->
<li>imperfect motion as non-zero-point embedding energy: centrifugal &gt; centripetal: demonic relation through the whole. valancy of bi- and uni-valence.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item -->

<!-- wp:list-item -->
<li>(at least) two imperfect motion in tension as imagination and projective visualization. this only gives the surface power for a mind.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item -->

<!-- wp:list-item -->
<li>third set of imperfect motion, forcefulness of outside, is what creates the three dimensional world. third set of imperfect motion is always fed to first perfect motion. hence, </li>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ol>
<!-- /wp:list -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>four motion makes a circle, 1 2 3 4     1 2 3 4, when looked from the perspective of meta-level teleological motion. But it itself must be curved when looked from enough broad time-frame.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>with regard to resemblences, one can make a circle twice faster, 1 2    3 4    1 2     3 4, and so on. This time, non-zero is the opposite of zero-point; and imagination is the opposite of concrete 3d objects;   zero-point coinciding with imagination, and, non-zero point coinciding with concrete 3d objects. And the former two is more powerful than the latter two. And the latter two are the more forceful ones. This is the tensions of four motions of being.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>But if the telos is not satistifed and the spiral is fragmented, vortex motion achieves like a non-tensive and exploding quality. This is the level of anti-teleological centripetality and not in the level of zero-pointness or non-zero-pointness.<br><br></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>188</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-07 02:22:45</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-06 23:22:45</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-19 03:39:11</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-19 00:39:11</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>vortex-motion-as-natural-motion-centripetal-and-centrifugal-two-cones-perfect-motion-concentric-as-stacking-of-vortices-zero-point-imperfect-as-non-zero-point-vectorality-non-natural-motion</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[s:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1674088754]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80313981186]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Insight as multi-layered generative thinking.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/07/insight-as-multi-layered-generative-thinking/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 20:44:29 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=202</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Fractality, non-equational recursion of a thinking pattern, working as a seed to be unfolded in the moment of thinking. Mis-fractality as a centrifugal degenerative thinking,  working as an exploding function, unstability. One-layered, univalent thinking as borderline states. Dis-embedding thinking veiled as "analytical," or rigorous. Relation of fractality with discoveries. Fractality sequentally unfolded as deductive reasoning. Multi-layeredness corresponds with multi-layerings of memory. Low frequency and high frequencies, overtonal analogy to thinking. Do one thinks thoughts or thoughts think one? Jungian perspectives, related to Story being. Psychoanalytic insight as an alignment of Logos and Pathos, pathology as mis-alignments.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>202</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-07 23:44:29</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-07 20:44:29</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-07 23:57:06</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-07 20:57:06</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>insight-as-multi-layered-generative-thinking</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[s:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1673125030]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80338136020]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1673124273]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Object relations of mis-toroidal. Internal vs. External. Here and There. And Pathologies.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/08/object-relations-of-mis-toroidal-internal-vs-external-here-and-there-and-pathologies/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 22:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=210</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><em>All object relations it the deformation of toroidal structure of psyche. In its healthy state Here and There is regulated and not to be identified. Here and there is different, and dynamically can be turned into one another. Torus internalize the external. Processes it, and externalizes. The projectivity of it is through the filamental calibration of insight, unfruitful projections can be backtraced, error can be studied. Learning and playing is the state of organism. ---- Three sicknesses: (1) Schizoid as the non-interfaced externalization of the internal, exactly by missing what is external. Eye of Here, cannot touch There. "Here" deforms. Here fragments into two, vivid (imaginative) and dull (real, social). There also becomes two, as the ideal and the real. There cannot be pulled into Here, and cannot be processed in this Torus. One internal realm is to be constructed with an extreme pedanticism, and all is referenced to that internality. This is what gives the manic'ness of the schizoid. But it is quite high-maintanence. Prone to vulnerabilities, induces nihilistic enantiodromic states. Manic states comes through inside, but the threat is from outside. (2) Borderline-Psychotic as the rumination of what is internal as if it is external. Because the energetic sensitivity to what is external is started to be lost, due to flattening and disembedding of the toroidal presence. Here becomes infinitely small, as the horizon narrows. Mind explodes, introjects and real world objects are the same. Privacy is not possible, everything generated Here is given to There (This is usually veiled as "radical honesty"). What is absent has the power to change everyting in the realm of presence. Even tough  the mode of presence is want to be monopolized, it is known that present and absent, Here and There is still different. Here is exploding, There, which is absent Here, is the absolute presence. At the boundary between PS and D, manic-ness can come from any direction as well as depression. Extreme suggestability. (3) Anti-schizoid-Anti-Psychotic: all external is internal, and no other internal is left.  Mirror image of all toroidality, as if all torus is schizoid.  Here and There is not different, there is only one type of presence: "witnessing" as the joint act of two minds. All seemingly internal is at a loss of the truth, hence must be witnessed to the real non-existence of itself, must be negated. A dejection where toroidal upset occurs. After, the truth-content existing as always a generated content of mind is injected, from Here to There, just as the borderline case, to what is external for the Other to be internalized by the Other, the movement is of one-valued centrifugality. And only the forceful dejection and injection has the value of Presence. There, before the act of wittnessing, is absent. Here, before the act, is absent as well. Here-there jointness is of the interface, and not all interfaces are PS. Some are depressive, to the non-existence, thus: Candidates of internalities must be polarized into two. Just as the schizoid toroidality fragmented into two--now, all toroidalities are fragmented into two. Depressive must be eliminated through injections, and the vicinity must be manic. All existing is "on the fly, " and no embedding is held. Cannot be held, due to one-layeredness of anti-toroidality of anti-schizoid state. But this will bring a side-effect: Since all uniques has embeddings, hence seems as an error to the anti-schizoid thinking, this erroneus by-product must be externalized as well. Since it is the anti-psychotic, psychoticizing content must be projected. This is what intensifies the polarization of the candidates.</em> This is all for a absolute schizoid structure to be build, which cannot be vulnerable in any way, but the exact working of it always deferred to the infinite, sometimes as anti-schizoid becoming schizoid, sometimes becoming anti-schizoid.<br><br>All three admits the oneness of subjective perspective: a form of self-absorption, or of Other-blindness, or of lacking of Self-Knowlegde, with changing degrees. And all three has some determinative power over another, hence create each other. as the trickster functions of the one in question. Hence, in a population, when some increases, some others must increase as well. Moreover, in the same organism, the toroidal state can switch between these three, depending on the ana- or cata-strophe of the situation and personal history. And mostly, these states, are imprinted into the ordinary character of humans, mostly sensed as the negative quirks of peers. From the ratio's between the borderline three (ego functions are lost to the point of poverty and non-execution in external world) and the more healthy, mildly neurotical ones (ego functions are stable) one can infer the health of a community and the rigidity of a community. In the exceedings of some threshold ratios, a community might explode, literrally, and metaphorically. In contrast, I suspect and believe that in a paleolithical-tribal society, there is not much room for a non-functional mis-toroidality, since Life and Death is always in front of the primate organism.  Just as there is not much mis-toroidality in animals, even in domesticated ones. Pets acts like a re-toroidalizer in a mis-toroidal household. Their animal pureness cannot be discharged, in most of the cases.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Four critical symptoms for mis-toroidality: </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(1) inability to be playful in a smooth manner. to be able to start a comical sitution and end. Determine the boundary between what is serious and not both in the level of play, and in a meta-level. Inability to play comes with inability to learn in an effortless manner. Only eccentric learning is left, further rigidifying anf fragmenting the etheric-animal intelligence. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(2) regulation of agression towards the other and towards the in-group member. inability to show anger, or inability to control anger. Anger is shown both to the beloved and to the hated, as a living regulation of distance. but all three cannot regulate distance, it is all or not. this will also include ability to take away criticism, or an insult. All boils down into the inability to understand an animalic sense of locality and of territory, which only one organism can be present at. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(3) inability to conduct any cleaning. both in physical and psychical realm. if a cleaning becomes too hard, or too pedantic, or too black-and-white; it achieves a gnostical, story-like form. Cleaning always becomes more than its candle. Hence, in order to clean an area, other necessarily becomes more unclean. Wastage occurs. Or worse, the close-vicinity becomes the thrashbin. Similarly, such attitude cannot smoothly bring any negative thought or emotion or insecurity or anticipation in a relationship in the fear of losing every positive side; thus, relationship comes in two forms, all white or all black, and no grey in between. But worse: No degrees of light and dark. No feedback regarding better or worse. No cathartical emotional experience is allowed in such states, if any unclean comes up it rubs of on every clean parts, hence re-traumatizing. Catharsis is impossible, and metastasis is the principle. In contrast, an animal if enough energy is present, always self-cleans without much wastage if any.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><em>All upper three is regarding this: Inability to work with the subtle differentiality and differing in degree in experiential life, differential, but containing heterogeneity and normativity, asymmetry regarding polarities. But is not uni-valent. And essentially linked with the three, a desire for static absolute perspective as a "non-perspective" emerges as: (This will confuse the right-hand-side of the schema of crux point, the digital-solidity, with the realm of change and what is beyond experience. The infinite, the absolute point of reference and the cause of all is incorrectly ascertained as solidity and sameness. A reversed ontology.)</em></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(4) Feeling of "the Eye" as present mostly out of body, always looking and judging at the things done and said. This eye becomes infinitely fractured in acute psychotic experiences. But is mostly chronically present in all mis-toroidal states of organism, sometimes internalized sometimes externalized. In latter, one projects the eye into the real organisms, confusing the inner solidifed and rigid (serotonergic) reality with the dynamic and real outside, mostly creating self-fullfilling prophecies in its life. Further, in such states, organism is not sensitive of the real looks and glanings over its body (Rupert Sheldrake studies the exact phenomena in "the Sense of Being Stared At.")---since a past glance made them extremely discharged and they could not become recovered, which is a disembedding past glance which in in fact traumatized by another past glance and so on. This is exactly what ancient traditions call "Evil Eye", or "Nazar" etc, and it passes through inter-generational re-traumatizations mostly in infancy or first years in life; or sometimes in the dramatical-catacylismic points in life.  The eye always look at the absolute internal realm which schizoid tries to establish. In various motions between the three mistoroidalities, "the Eye" also moves, but always tried to be maintained as "one." If not, psychosis comes, an explosion as an undecidability of the one and the infinite Eye. In order to defer psychosis, all mistoroidal hyperverbalizes always self-explaining and externally justifying the unexamined action of its toroidality, either to its introjects, non-audible, or to the external real ones, audible. It self-discharges. It wastes its own energy.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Eventually and sadly, anti-toroidal makes one anti-toroidal---usually in the guise of education, or relationship, or family. And all these four contributes to one's not being able to feel "any real territorial safety," and "peace"--all growth is in a local vivid safety. Mis-toroidal slowly losts its territory, become landless. Antichtonic unaware to its own serotonergy-Downward motion, eventually becoming anti-etherical-of the Upward. In the ever-present increases in "Fear of Breakdown," to use the term of Winnicott which correctly describes the vorticity of the phenomena. Fear of Breakdown induces and couples with its counterpart fears of other breakdowns. Fear gnawing on the hope, to the point that every corner is filled only with fear. And the global significance of such a fear cannot be studied sematically, only must be escaped in an hypnotic state. No learning can happen because this one gnawing movement cannot be "unlearned." The organism becomes a prisoner in a low-energy and dis-embedded toroidal states, which act as feedback loops wasting energy. When new energy comes, usually it induces mania, hence again thrusts the system into wastage and the further same feedback loops. If serotonergy of the organism cannot be reversed in an anti-serotonergical interventions, and the internalization of such experience; and if an anti-serotonergical state cannot be calibrated with a sense of what etherical energy  and what self-soothing of a toroid exactly is, if the childlike euphoria (which always comes in an etherical or anti-serotonergical intervention) cannot be contained and controllably fed the learning and new habitual patterns.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>This is the dynamics of trauma, which is lost in most of the trauma literature, where only its stasis is left, only imprintings of it as the rigidity, only its residues. Psychology and psychiatry is in its Decay states, traumatized by the external forces which are in fact the subject-matter of the exact profession. Professionals themselves are usually falling into chronical learned-helpnesses either induced externally or induced internally through their own familial trauma. Just as organism grows in its toroidality finding new forms which is of the same center zero-point; an organism can decay in its anti-toroidal states losing energy, discharged uncontrollably and drained, resulting from facing with ec-centrizing non-zero-points, the forcefulness of life which is always experienced as "external." In such a sense, external forces if it can be endured safely, always hints a possibility for a new Growth, in the presence of insight and enough etherical energical charging.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>(The forceful is not a person but a force or forces, for it is or they are not one.  To assume the forceful as a person is to be in a over-projective and over-protective state, hence is to be discharged into an anti-toroidal state. This is the transferential mistake of psychiatry---a healing science itself in sick health. You cannot save someone by overprotecting them as sickly frail child, or over-projecting them as a sick person. -- A force is not one, but a derived difference between two one's, admitting externality. Zero-pointness is always what primary admits oneness and implosion, hence, internality. Non-zero admitting forcefulness and two'ness, not oneness. A straight line is derived from vortex motion or from circle, as being its centrifugal derivative in one moment. And not vice-versa. A vector is not one. Rather a circular motion is one. Only with the tension of one'ness and two'ness-es, wihtin an encapsulating one'ness, can one create three dimensionals: Platonic solids, occuring and determining factor of all phases, not only in solidity. One, two, three. Exactly mapped with dimensionalities.) </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Force is external. This is exactly what people mean when they are stating a draining situation or a draining person. The forcefulness is always outer-auric, not, absent, but "changes in degres" with respect to where and when the toroidal present at. Some externalities of some where's are admitting more absence than others: That is to say, some territories are draining for toroidal, or say, anti-territories. When such drainage achieves some critical states, pathology takes over (in an automata-like way, triggered externally and re-enacted every time it is called, with a different content in real world thus veiling its "loop"-like manner) and over-rigidifies the experience to the point of no growth and no decay can be studied, and organism is stuck at its learned helpnessness and hopelessness.  In a negative feedback loop, with a centrifugal vortex motion, it explodes and dis-embeds some parts of the inner-toroidal-helix: Wounds the energical body and blocks the peristalsis of soul (downsetting of the toroidal, its filamental and beam-like ratio). The tragical part is that, the exact points of such dischargeing are lost, becomes as if "between the lines," which only a subtle and "a forensic" toroidal intuition can be aware of. The real causality is always veiled within the mis-causality of mild or of severe trauma.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><em>The possibility of healing as being more than before. Positive side of trauma.</em> <em>Trauma as the stepping stone.<br></em><br><em>The vortex dynamics of the three anti-toroidalities is quite intricate. Look at the particle psychicist Vaknin, take the most interesting part</em>, and apply it into a dynamical psychics. <em>Inspect literary tensions as the vortex relation of the three. </em><br><br>Try to visualize the de-toroidal forms of the three pathologies. And the resulting state transitions will come up as personality disorders. Dynamics can create various particularities. Wave and frequency thinking. personality disorders as dual or triplet relations between 2-d shapes or platonic solids. The system is more basic than we thought in modern psychology. Relation of the solid-shape relations with the heart-explosion tension. Relations with Winnicot's Fear of Breakdown.<br><br>Geometrical Psychology, or the science of representation., by B.W. Betts, Louisa S Cook<br>https://ia903404.us.archive.org/31/items/geometricalpsych00cook/geometricalpsych00cook.pdf </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>210</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-08 01:26:07</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-07 22:26:07</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-09 04:07:15</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-09 01:07:15</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>object-relations-of-mis-toroidal-internal-vs-external-here-and-there-and-pathologies</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1673130370]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[s:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1673226439]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80339962558]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Triangle, of Life and Death. Re-generation, de-generation, mis-generation.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/08/triangle-of-life-and-death-re-generation-de-generation-mis-generation/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 02:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=237</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Which can be applied all phases of experientiality, as a tension between reductant and oxidant forces. Here in the tension, the external aspect of forcefulness must be construed and not zero-points. Zero-points are mostly re-generative. Stability and unstability as the residual processes: that is, two dis-embeddings, admitting stasis and ek-stasis. A theory of idolatry, and diabolicism. Story of Iblis, islamic idolatry, of soil and of fire.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>237</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-08 05:15:46</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-08 02:15:46</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-08 05:15:46</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-08 02:15:46</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>triangle-of-life-and-death-re-generation-de-generation-mis-generation</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[u:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1673144240]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80343611333]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1673144149]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Non-projective War. Defence of Locality.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/08/non-projective-war-defence-of-locality/</link>
  <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 03:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=264</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><em>Decentralized resemblences. "Do not tread on me," the liberal symbolism. Evil as always external aggregated forcefulness, and not as the Enemy per se. The Evil is not one. The Evil cannot be eliminated. Forcefulness also forces one to make the Evil into a "one" and hence commit a projection. Being at real war, as the non-projective holding of tension within the forcefulness of the current state, choosing the most apt strategy for the Life of implosion and of what is most valuable, which can change with regard to locality and privacy. Schmitt's last war analogy. Stasiology as Love encapsulating all, but also the non-Love as the tension between. Boundary defence as negation of the negative: the projector boundary-defences. Auric, territorial defence as the living-animalic-trophic defence.</em> Real war is always in layers. (1) Internal: Civil war within the toroidal, war between true self and false self. (2) Boundary-condition: Experiential tension between embedding and dis-embedding. Hence healty projection. (3) External: Gnostic war, politico-theology: as the inclusive and exclusive membrane between alchemical and what seems as alchemical,  or what is transmutative or what seems last-transmutative, philosopher's stone and absolute-pharmakon, promethean-techne vs. singularity as the explosion of technics, absolute-techne. Matter of digitality as what defines being "elites." Possesions as the digital solidity. Possesive power of digital value, non-alchemization processes, "elite," or "the authority" as the possessed. Platonic counterparts as those who must govern and those who currently try to govern. Re-thinking as the tension between one and many, within the realm of experience. Enemy or evil projecting as the most unfruitful strategy of war. Trickster functions. Most apt warrior as those who can self-sense the global significance of manipulative-trickster processes, he who can look into the double-bind of the War Sign. Warrior as the outer layer of Magician. Meaninglessness of modern warfare, and most wars. "Casus belli" as the bouncings between borderline and neurotic states, as the tables turning phenomena. Who decides on the Enemy: Can "prote ergo obligo" be eliminated? Sovereign intuition, and anti-sovereign counterparts. Can serotonergy be eliminated? Degrees with respect to eliminative instinct. Outer layer cannot make sense as separate. A fractal solution for sect formations. Fractal solution to all war. Only de-escalation is Love-like. Real lover only de-escalates. Escalation as the PS. Christ-impulse. Last war instinct as the mis-causality and mis-unfolding of fractal solution. The solution is not time-wise, but it is local-space-wise. Last-War instict is related to distancing, not ending as putting an absolute timely end. Atraction and repulsion comes in heterogeneity. Former continues the presence of attracted in Here. Latter discontinues the presence from Here. Real instinct is light, non-projective, and imprints the warlike on sand, is of the "bygones" and elegant.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>264</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-08 06:25:18</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-08 03:25:18</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-08 06:49:49</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-08 03:49:49</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>non-projective-war-defence-of-locality</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[u:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1673149792]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80344704099]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1673148321]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Peristalsis in general.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/09/peristalsis-in-general/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 01:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=315</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Peristalsis in physical body. Peristalsis in psychical body. Relation of two toroidality is in timelines or spatiality. Spin of torus, and various references of spin. Ray Peat's anti-endotoxicity. Terrain Theory and Germ Theory, Bechamp and Pasteur. Resemblence of internal-toroidality to external-toroidality. Schizoid problems can be derived from the implosiveness or explosiveness of such a resemblence function. Meaning of isolation and spoilage, clostridium. And meaning of claustrum, chrysm.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>315</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-09 04:35:56</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-09 01:35:56</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-09 04:35:56</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-09 01:35:56</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>peristalsis-in-general</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[u:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1673228300]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80370218483]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1673228159]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Does an emanation in crux decrease the whole? Ana-strophe, and catastrophe. Akashic.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/11/does-an-emanation-in-crux-decrease-the-whole/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 01:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=321</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><em>Relate it to global serotonergical processes, and the sequentialities between event contexts, between spatio-temporalities, between God-occurences. Anamnetic de-residualizations, and residualities as the chronological Sema, exactly hinting the route of re-incarnation sequences. Relation of separate memories of different Lifes. Global serotonergical signal, always renews, but in its giving state, it acts as if Godhead is decreased, so that the entropical trickster Sema can be seen and answered regeneratively,  new Life starts, global serotonergy re-news.</em></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>The whole has an etherical fabric, as the most primary "context." The infinite takes place in the ether, as electrics and sematics as its potentialization and actualization processes. It takes place and takes time: Ether as spatiotemporal realm. Event is contains what is in it, four elements emerge in sequence as the structure: Plasma, pneuma, liquid, solid. Sense, question, induction, deduction. Life is, at the threshold between the whole-the infinite, and the finite (structure), in the etherical interface. Both matter and soul dies far away from the infinite, it is the last point as finitude. Sedimentation, coagulation, externalization, objectification. The most differentiated part of the whole, away from the whole, to the point that if the parts are summed, the whole cannot be re-attained. Events dies as objects. Regeneration dies as degeneration. Even so, degeneration can show the way for a possible future regeneration. Decay is not extremely distinct from Growth, rather, it is in Growth, but not a Growth. <br><br>Neg-entropy, which is the name started to use at the beginnings of cybernetical science. In contrast to entropical processes which all mainstream termodynamical science studies as a basic principle. Here, the opposite attitude will be taken.<br><br>Most basic tension in universe:<br><br>What takes place in the main context as the neg-entropic zero-point energical processes as a whole are broad and over and more powerful than the entropical fragmentary forcing processes, in two senses: (1) Negentropy is prior in existence, by causally, logically, spatiotemporally coming first. (2) The entropy, if no priority can be found, can show a special type of Sema, which acts as "a tension in ether," to show the new way for regeneration. That is, the priority is not linear but circular, Neg-Entropy, can feed from the Entropical forces, either by burning away the residue, or by feeding from it. Ouroborics of regeneration shows that fire is prior to its ashes, and the ashes can fuel the new fire. The ashes are what is homogenized after Event takes place, as the absolute zero, but as what is most distant to zero-point energy.<br><br>That is to say, even Growth itself can grow. Total energy in the universe is not unchanging, let alone Decaying. (Hence Termodynamical laws must be re-ordered beyond its degenerative form.) <br><br>Presently existing universe can be transmuted, total energy can always increased, within the infinity. This is the ultimate God-making process, radical transmutation of given universe. And the Decay, or de-generation, always given in a fork: (1) A particulay decay as in Decay. (2) A particular decay as in Growth. (1) As if all local is Decaying or nothing is changing. (2) or as if a residual trickster sign for a new re-generation to occur. New energy sometimes being distant to its residue (Anabolism is always chosen by the etherically inclined) sometimes re-calibrating, or cleaning, or burning its residue (Catabolic pathways are re-regulated). And this is the ultimate war encapsulated by Love.  And when the exact burning relation itself oxidized into a higher state, system will residue into another Decay state to be Grown over. Hence Decay shows itself as non-Growth, but it can be used up and erased by new-Growth.<br><br>Neg-entropy as more powerful than Entropy.<br><br>And the basic daimonics or ethics as: <br><br>Do you part on the side of Neg-Entropy, always re-charging and not wasting any energy? Or, Do you part on the side of entropy, striving to sediment the most decayed form of Decay?<br><br>Ultimately opposing and burning the decaying attitude of Decay: "If more energy comes Here, it must be taken from somewhere. Life in this place is always a death in another place." To such an attitude, one may step beyond: In actuality, the presupposition of a closed system itself is a sedimentation of previous energical process, even if true and can be shown in a discretized system. That is, attitude itself is Dead and discharging the neg-entropic one by dis-embedding a discontinuity from its continuity. So, one have to look at formative process at the exact Presence, reverting the disembedding act into Here and Now. And in a global look, can infinitude itself diminish in some way in any particular increasings of it? Even if in particular decayings it does not decay it the most global sense. Energizing of the locality is the sublimating process of Here and hence a God-making. Every anabolism may have a catabolic counterpart coming in time-wise later, or place-wise non-zero vacuum (one can trace, for instance, the new energy coming from our sun from its filaments, is a discharging of some other zero-point in some other interstellar system); but this does not a equilibrium process of the infinite, but only a residual finitude. Within the scope of infinite, energy is given to the Sun so that it transmute it so that to increase the net-energy in its presence: Anastrophe. This is the opposite of Wastage. Waste still can occur in the process if some embedding goes wrong, named as Catastophe (Poleshift in star-wise, planet-wise, and organism-wise, is always of wastage. Velikovsky's corpus is a study of this in macro terms. Psychiatry as an organism-wise poleshift, is not studied enough, other than Peat's negative attitude towards excitation, or Wilson's admitting Life as a Down phenomena). And exactly the waste itself, not-being-able-to-actualize-the-anticipated-actualization, or falling-short-of, or "potential and actual becoming far away from themselves=unable to touch," is of the Entropical processes and not the other way around.  Please look at your own Life in the light of such tension between anastrophic neg-entropical embedding/power and catastrophic entropical forces. Between Fecundity and Wastage.<br><br>Will to barrenness and to wastage is of the Decay attitude. Will to Fecundity is not wasteful (to assume otherwise is entropic; treating the neg-entropy as if it is the invading of another point's energy), rather, it contains the energy ultimately and literally. It contains the polarity of centripetaly and centrifugality, and embedding of continuous energy, in order to be sensitive and to be thoughful to new breath and new question of the moment---in contrast to discontinuing and discretizing into its vectoral components, decomposing itself. Will to Cecundity, contains the new energization, it does not like "to be bled," or "to be disembedded" by a aldready-known forcings hence being a product of old and barren energical residue formations. It knows that blood (metaphorical and literal, as etherical life force (dodecahedron and icosahedron is duals), as the continuous embedding, and becomes dis-embedded if coagulated) is an etherical currency (currency in its most vivid and context-dependent sense, along with its time and place) and must be saved for the best. It desires for higher energy and curious for unknown forcings, hence, taking its time and place, saves and uses the energy for the new Sema, exactly for the next sublimatory processes, and hence the new energizations unknown in the present. With internal control and internal auto-motivity.<br><br>This God-making motion has infinite pathways, God is made in infinite localities, in the infinite main contexts of the whole. Because between what is infinite and what is finite, the occuring energy transition is not of a closed system. Even between two finitized systems, there may be an openness, since for what one had the necessity to seperate and interface them other than an interface of them with the infinite? Universe is an open God-making process(es), in its infinite moments. Hence, de Chardin's Omega Point as the end of residual processes as the new regeneration, always coming with an etherical rememberence and purging of a blocking residual memory. System, if open, always backtraces into its etherical re-formative states. The energy coming is both transmuted to radiant peripheral energy, and ultimately to a beamlike upward energy, which is ultimately studied in ancient east as Kundalini, and in Christianity as Chrism, and in various spiritual or scientific epochs in various names. <br><br>Death (ultimate Decay) as an impossiblity in two steps, where the latter open is more powerful than the former closed: (1) Energy is not lost, if unchanging, goes somewhere, but (2) it is ever-growing, it is always increased, with a view to and in the perspective of next neg-entropical moment. And perspectivality is always of neg-entropic, infinite zero-points having ana-strophic transmutative relation and sequence between them: Meaning of akashic records with a view to bio-energetics. (And the catastrophic relation and sequence must also held in ethericity as a shadow of it. As a reference to the mis-toroidality entry, this alone can have the power to explain inter-relational traumas.) This is how theosophists like Steiner or some other mediums/clairvoyants can ascertain two past lifes as a continuation of one another. They can feel and study re-incarnative routes. Or with a view to Peat's ideas, consciousness as a standing wave within neutrino sea (other name for neg-entropical zero-point within ether), can be watched from another zero-point; life as a continuation of other, with different count and persistances of physical bodies (tetrahedral to hexahedral structures and their residues).<br><br>From there, one can speculate: Serotonin (via Peat's definition) always mediate coagulation in the presence of dis-embedding, bleeding of charge, irritation, hence a micro-Death. If somewhere in the body is inflamed, you feel that particular place. You de-exist into bleeding and coagulation, de-exist elementally in the sequnce of etherical-&gt;liquid-&gt;solid. This is the negative Pathos. It can occur both physically and psychically, both are regulated by HPA axis in endocrine system. Such state, psychologically sediments also, fall the mind into a prey of entropical thinking: This makes the mind hold unto one entry point to its memory, it rigidifies the memory, un-anamnetically, as a residue memory: i.e. memory as exactly what blocks the backtracing movement. So it an hold only its own decomposition, and the cause of it as the anticipated chain of events, triggerred externally and hence an illusory cause. It is the memory of fear and loss, and of closure. For instance, one cannot forget a quite damaging event in the past, always re-enacting it projecting it into the future. (Relate it to Winnicott's fear of breakdown. Or relate it to Alchemical nigredo, or putrefactio.) And invokes unability to forget the initiator of Decay. Serotonin regulates the blocking memories, absolute imprintings. As if a memory destroys the possiblity of new memories. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>However, in contrast, local pain invokes the global pain. And the scenario as entropical as it is, it can give the possiblity of the fork as a particular decay and more broad Growth. The latter is "present" as the absent in the serotonergical memory. It must invoke one to read between the lines; lines being serotonergical blocking-memories in the memory. Global pain works as a fork Sema, signalling next life. Possibility of next neg-entropy. When new energy comes and memory de-residualizes, one can transmute its Decay signal into its next form, and change the psychical content of serotonergy in its next coming. This is a recipe for re-incarnating, both in this Life and in other Lifes. Such a re-newing can have its concentric identities throughout one life, and this is no other than a spiritual concept of soul making a contract before coming into its current incarnation. Whole spiritual tradition have its electrical and sematical science in the tension between neg-entropy and entropy, and here, the exact dynamics of it must be studied, both with a view to electromagnetics and bioenergetics of the situation, and the signalling relations of it.<br><br>Peat's brilliance is to be able to sense the interrelations between local biological meaning of serotonin and more global political and physical-philosophical sense of serotonin as a Decay-signal. Here, we must take one step more, and say that, any Decay-signal also signals unknown Growth. This is not to say that one must delve into every particular serotonin cascade. Not at all. Serotonin cascades and chronical serotonin syndromes are the cancer of society, both metaphorically and literally. And one must fly away from cancer of mind and of body as much as possible. Rather, with periodical and heterogeneous anti-serotonergic interventions, one can see serotonin as a global Decay-signal, that is, one does not take it as a closing and localizing, but calls its bluff, seeing the fork as both closing Decay and in Growth in an anastrophical sense. "No pain no gain" attitude is uncalibrated serotonergically, it loses its anastrophic meaning and insight, falling into barren masochism of progress without direction. Rather, one must limit the serotonin cascade, almost eliminate it, but still must be able to smell where the cascade points at. This is the trickster tension between Growth and Decay. This broadens the possibility for new transmutation, by studying the exact "stasiology" at the crux point of experience. Negentropy can either burn up the pointed direction if deciding the meaninglessness of it in its embedding insight by leaving the ashes at nothingness, or can be fed up by the ashes by digesting its degeneration. Ouroborical principle here, either backtracing without digesting or with digesting. (This is the radical interdependence between energy and structure, energy being more prior but feeding.) In all cases, memory retrieved into its non-blocking akashical state: memory as a etherical-tension chain for God-making processes, between the previous lesser-God and next higher-God. This memory is externalized and sedimented as mythology, in the human history. But may possibly have various disguises in both our history and in other life-form's histories.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>321</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-11 04:46:48</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-11 01:46:48</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-12 02:37:00</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-11 23:37:00</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>does-an-emanation-in-crux-decrease-the-whole</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1673401611]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[s:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1673480224]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80433033591]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[(Un)reality inside Words: Relation of Simulation and Serotonin.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/18/reality-inside-words-simulation-and-serotonin-relation/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 00:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=395</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Algorithm's relation to spiral movement. Linear cascading and triggering of loops or state machines in human world, or in cave. Started with false self triggerings, triggerings as univalences, or as not being able to receive the double bind in the fluid intelligence which works in differentiality-degrees. Serotonin as the main rigidifier of body and mind. Thought processes becomes externally controlled and algorithmic and space-time-serotomemory triggered, instead of concentric, embedded and spiralic. <br></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>In order for any programming occur, liquid motion as the starter of program and solidity must be interfaced. This is the start. And the framing and exact programming, only occurs with key-lock relations of solid-rigid bodies. This is the principle of mechanism. Programming is solid, hence, of serotonergic. All types of programming from neuro-linguistic to punched-card to a implemented turing machine, works in such way. The dents or holes or half-conducting routes which electrical current flows and cut off through analog-digital filters works by the way of solid imprintings and triggered-machines. Exactly, where you put your dents as solid-memory, stays the same for the next fetching: this is spatial;  and the periodical checkings, readings, or dentings, writings, are discretely accessing memory: this is temporal. Spatial and temporal solidity is a necessary condition.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><br>Linearity as a "perfect" circular motion but started from outside, circle having its center from without. Views of halting problem in everyday strifings of animal loops: "tail chasing," behaviour in all animals, most intricate in human narrow-non-intelligence. rigid intelligence narrowed so that no broad loop can be seen.<br><br></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Anti-serotonin interventions as having a simulation breaking power.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Hypnosis breaking as a perspective shift of circle centered outside: unfolded as "?", revealing the toroidal structure of simulative spherics. But, hypnosis breaking is not un-folding or dis-embedding of insighted everyday motion: Traditional "Socratics" may not be a real hypnosis-breaking.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Re-hypnotizing as calibrated and as uncalibrated. Former is of liquid-crystalline ego, not inflating, only doing in a blisfull way, what it supposed to do in a given ethical moment, daimonically intervened and re-programmed constantly. Uncalibrated hypnosis is prone to its trickter hypnotizations, stays in a never-ending fueling-oxidizing relation, or in a city, minor-depression and hypo-mania inducing relations.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>395</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-18 03:39:35</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-18 00:39:35</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-18 04:23:43</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-18 01:23:43</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>reality-inside-words-simulation-and-serotonin-relation</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[s:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1674005026]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80647062329]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1674002378]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Serotonin as a possible etheric time-stamp proto-object signifying local solidity context.]]></title>
  <link>https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/2023/01/18/serotonin-as-a-possible-etheric-time-stamp-object-signifying-solidity-context/</link>
  <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 20:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>electricsemiotic</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://electricsematic.wordpress.com/?p=404</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>marking the causal bottleneck, creating a local simulative environment.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>How what is etheric, can veil the etheric? </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Local:</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>all objects casually connected to a proto-object, this creates its beginning and end and its ordinary time-span. Without proto-object, no object can be in time and space.  -- similarly, all candidates of real knowledge implies either an opinion or natural law: both are local. Serotonin or the equivalent of serotonin in pre-biological realm, as any kind of Thanatic signal, or say Entropic signal, may cause the local opinionation or lawfulness to clockwork, until the new deus ex "machina" intervenes and changes the law, miracle. exception is pre-serotonergic, from the space-time-stamp, given-lawfulness is created. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Global:<br>the spatio-temporality of toroidality, and non-spatio-temporality of god-head, non-emanated infinite. <br><br>Candidates for a global serotonergy, or akashic records:<br><br><em>say </em>:<br><em>(e) : total existing neg-entropy and its filamentality is emanated god </em><br><em>(s) : the source of the total neg-entropy, infinitude beyond existing infinitude</em><br>(t) : this toroidality or this neg-entropy, zero-point which is Here and Now.<br><br>1. Relation of (t) to (e). <br>2. of (t) to (s)<br>3. of (e) to (s)<br>4.1 of non-biological (t) (gnosis or knowledge, which can grow on toroidalities in different time and spcae) to (e), 4.2. or non-biological (t) to (s)<br>5. of this given (t) to non-given but with same center-point of zero-point (t)<br>6. of non-biological (t) to (t) : sometimes serotonin dosage  signifies and pinpoints one's particular knowledge production and its objects.<br>7. of this (t) to that (t), different center points, within the same smooth space-time continuity: tensive<br>8. of two (t)'s having different center points within different discontinuous space-time: past/future lifes<br><br><br>(3) becomes the relation between a completed god to the god.  This is a teleological end-point of a incarnative route to the infinitude of incarnative god-routes.<br>(2) is what separated with biological born</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>It is important to differentiate, toroiddality seperating itself from filamentality and grows, is not solidification from infinite universe. And it is not the death of total energy: for this would be fall in to a hoax of entropic thinking. if torus growing here grows, it is primarily because of the source of all neg-entropy, and not because energy is coming from elsewhere, and when it is stopped, the growth will end. Life Here is not a local death of infinitude, rather, it is a further Life, an increment of infinitude, since it has not upper end limit in degree and in intensity. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>But how then, seperation of toroidality from infinite in any above sense admit serotonergy? It is important to differentiate between locality and solidification, or locality and entropy. But see this: An Entropy is from toroidality is not from the source of neg-entropy. Source of neg-entropy causes neg-entropy, this is of the phases of reality. That is local ridigity as absolute is emanated from local as local. Local as local is emanated from what is cannot be globalized. If Entropical De-Context is the sedimentation of primary locality as toroidality, then it must be of the same motion in actuality. Then the rigidification motion is to be understood primarily etherical. But as a peculiarity of ether as the self-veiling of itself. Serotonin is this. <br><br>Some signs veils their source, an uncalibrating-sign. <br><br>Science of akasha must re-calibrate any uncalibrating-thanatic-entropic-sign. Time-stamping power of torus, platonic solids, vibrational relations must be studied. Serotonin both time-stamps then rigidifies, time-stamp itself becomes veiled and admitting absolutism hence veiling of timeless-ness as given eternality. (this is the same for that assuming the sameness admitted in digital cubism (last entropical deadline of reality) as if it is what is beyond change: most ridiculous form of idolatry which most of philosophy falls into probably because most of the philosophical practice itself is uncalibratingly serotonerging and lipid peroxidative hence anti-pneumatic with rare exceptions.)<br><br>This must also show a seditive science's acts of separation regarding knowledge and information. For insance, how physics seperated from psychology, or regarding </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>-<br>Etherical timestamping Sema must be bi-valued, at broader level it is bounded to a neg-entropical zero point, at narrower level, it shows the direction for an entropical de-context.<br><br>~<br>upper paragraphes must be anti-serotonergically re-calibrated. too complex, too much distinctions.<br><br>How a psychic can tune into a triggered memory-loop within a scene? <br>may be related: <br><br>Itzhak Bentov, <em>Stalking the Wild Pendulum: On the Mechanics of Consciousness</em><br>https://www.cia.gov/readingroom/docs/CIA-RDP96-00788R001700210016-5.pdf </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>404</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-01-18 23:35:16</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-01-18 20:35:16</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-01-19 02:21:38</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-01-18 23:21:38</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>serotonin-as-a-possible-etheric-time-stamp-object-signifying-solidity-context</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[s:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1674084101]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[80674703496]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
  </channel>
</rss>
